You didn't raise your voice, you didn't raise your hand, just stood there quiet like you didn't understand, but I saw your eyes, you knew the shape of it, so-
Second pause in the room reset someone laughs it off someone just forgets you call it be sick all the stage control
They said let it go said don't make it worse, but no one has
This hour at the table
Just whatever's true to say
this is familiar circling down each one wearing a face you carved yourself i'm the one chair that
doesn't sit on the shelf not in the frame adjacent to the picture the plain seat for the man behind
the scripture you don't need another mirror another
The daughter needs a song, the family needs a 330
It's true
What happened someone form on me or something like I left so I left for like five minutes two more hours
Whatever, I probably won't be here for much longer anyway, so
Enjoying why I'm here
Everyone who give me shit about all my stuff
It's like
Yeah
I left them up for like five minutes. It's so good my channel got taken down for like nudity
Thank you, charisma. Thank you
I mean I try to do cool stuff, but
Everyone just complains
Thanks
Well, there is I was here for ten minutes there's no one here, so I put on a six-minute song, but
Here, well, you're gonna complain all this play
You don't know me yesterday
Just this hour at the table
Just whatever's true to say
You built a council
This is familiar circling down, each one wearing a face, you carved yourself
I'm the one chair that doesn't sit on the shelf
Not in the frame, adjacent to the picture
The plain seat for the man behind the scripture
You don't need another mirror, another voice that loves you
You need the one that won't inflate above you
leaking just the truth and what you do with that i'm i'm i'm the
I need you to hold the daughter
imagine dragons. Imagine being we can ugly and trying to find a
reason to find me unattractive. I fucking have seen your face
and you're fucking ugly as fuck. Get out of here. Thank you. I
don't hate you. I hate him. I hate that guy. Big tall, sexy,
big tall, ugly or short bald, ugly rod.
The link is
Then post it. I'm sorry
Thank you, I
Don't know why it's not coming through
Then came to you saw me. We'll take a good look might be the last time you never know
This I don't know much longer. This channel will be up. So
Enjoy it while it lasts
I just want to come back on one more time just to like hang out but
Everyone's fucking so mean
Just like be that well, that's that's one of the qualifications. Okay. Well, probably will
But I don't know you well enough
Hi, I wasn't gonna come up here like throw a party for you
But I will say but like you kind of like I had a boner when I seen you earlier
I was like, damn, so he's like, give me a bone.
You're looking out of shit.
Well, yeah.
That's, uh, I don't talk, actually.
That's flattering.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Oh my gosh.
I'm moved.
Your team's psyche.
Thank you so much.
Will you know what's weird?
When I went on beat-a-stream,
my dick inverted back into my stomach.
It actually, you like, inverted back in.
Like, remember, like, when the Wizard of Oz,
when the Witch's sister got ran over by a house
and her legs were sticking out?
I don't know. That's basically what Bita does. That's Bita. Bita's the house, and I'm the legs that are sticking out.
I don't know if I'm thankful for Obamog because I think he pawned on me.
That was cool as shit when he was walking around Germany the other day drinking beer. That's cool that you let him on panel though.
You're a good guy. It's like you always let him on.
It's like the last stream. The last stream taking that for New York.
Oh, we got nude. Oh, we actually got naked. Oh
Happen just even know where there's less you might take it down. I wasn't even watching it at the time
I should be watching my own stream, but um
All of a sudden it was just down. It's a sexual sexual and nude content or something like that
I know like, you know one thing I didn't at least say be the never went real life on me
Like it's be to anybody in the chat. Hold on. Let me look at the chat. Does anybody ever on real life?
Oh, hold on somebody say a beat it went real life on me. What what happened man? It's threatening talk talk to me
He's on no offense like you but it's like he shut your gay mouth
What does she do to you when she went real life?
Don't say shut his mouth it says panel don't ever talk to him
Yeah, how about you shut your mouth straight up okey shut your mouth so we get fucking listening to this clip
Thank you
Don't ever live with me
Have you ever seen a good-looking man because I'm looking at one right now and he's in the middle of this yeah
Have you ever seen a dumb dumb? So I'm looking at one right now. He's on the left of the chat. Oh
What are you looking at a mirror? You're looking at a mirror and you see a dumb dumb that's you dumb
How did that make sense? I said left of the chat. I'm gonna make sense to me or you do you look straightforward?
You're not gonna disrespect my boy. Yeah, straight up
Well, if I disrespected my eyes, he's
Shut up. There's like a lover today. He's actually like a lover today. Okay. Oh
million love stories, right?
So why don't you do your story straight tea? Oh because when they get they be mean to you because that's what that's what hey
How do you know they like
Dumdum has a brain I got a brain
Tea
Joe are you not gonna
Are you not gonna come up you're not gonna compliment his shirt
at least
you know what, I would bite that shirt off of it
I would eat that shirt off
like psyche be like Joe, why are you biting my shirt
I'm like psyche, I'm taking that shirt off with my teeth
you understand
wow
is that too farty, is that too much for you
ah no no, I'm comfortable, well psyche is my best friend so
I mean, we get weird after years sometimes
It's only going to get worse
If I was on a like a different platform, would you would you go watch my show there? I mean look, it's like your house. He's single
He's so fucking handsome. Yeah, how are you single good question? Let's let's let's debate this guy
They don't even I don't date and it's like and people think I'm like, aww
Married so you don't date at all at all
Or just nobody here. Which one here's all here this fucking
I don't know me. Oh, I mean, I'm sure I could find some. Oh, you're just sticking it in any time you can do it
And you just sticking it in. I don't think
Three Adams apples
I've got you to swallow
I dare you to shut the fuck up, Joe. I only I spit it on
I dare you
I'm sorry. I didn't even hear that. I'm not going to lie to you. I'm glad you didn't hear it.
Okay. Let's all calm down. Let's all calm down here, Joe. Yeah. Let's see. How is everybody doing?
I mean, I was there to shut up. I was there to shut up. I was feeling really... Yeah, you were there to shut up, but you distilled.
At least it's really gay, but see coming out of the closet man. You're gay man. See be honest
That's very rude. That's like me calling. That's like me calling.
That's what turns me on about sluggy at least you miss his sexuality
I would have chopped that green tree. Yeah, thank you. It was picky on ghosts
who's to pick on ghosts and it's not that he's
Ain't nobody gonna pick on me. I'll fuck him up when it's out of here. What are you still here?
I fuck with it that is and be this week. Is that beat us? Oh, no. What does it say beta has a week or beta has a wide badge?
You remember all those nights that protect it, you know, can you protect me just making fun of me?
We'll protect
I'm in my feet feet
If you're gonna cry about it, I'm crying right now psyche. Can you protect me?
Did anybody protect me, please? Like yeah, we're protecting now who the fuck you think you're talking to you know
You're talking that goes boy. You better shut the fuck up. Don't talk to me like that ever again
Yeah, and a rare way stop bringing us up. Don't play with me. It's not funny
We're not fucking sitting up here like fucking
Don't play with me like that. We're not friends like that. Don't play with me first of all second of all
psyche how you doing? well i was talking to psyche to be honest i wasn't talking to psyche to be honest
anyway psyche how you doing? i'm okay how are you?
well i thought you were in a bad mood you piece of shit you piece of shit
I
This channel because
Who did this porn bomb or somebody that is sick at their wiener, but it's like why does your friend?
Psychi, why does your fancy have a speech impediment? He has like a speech impediment
No, that's what you do
Like a list T. Why do you have a list?
Look at the nor looking at you take she's there right at you
God bless you Lenore
of the
the
Oh, I thought you said another word. I'm gonna be on this channel. No
I know how you talk, bro. I've ever seen you in real life, too. You know what I would do to you
Hug me and buy me a drink and we can go out and hang out. No, I'm gonna rape you. I would actually rape you. Hey
Oh my fucking god, you can't say that on YouTube. We're not on your mobile. I just got done explaining that.
Great beer. Great beer. I saw it.
Oh, okay.
Even that's fucking crazy though.
Why would you say that though?
Yeah, why would you say that?
Cuz I want yeah, yeah, you're fucking you're a moron dog
Why are you up here? You just call me then where to
You're paying the psyche
What are you gonna do about it tea? Oh my name is tea
I don't know. I don't know. Um, but, um, yeah.
So Chris Land has been like streaming like, you know, Brandon, um,
Q and like, then Brandon Q is like streaming her back.
And it's like, they're both like talking to each other, like threads.
And then they're, they're all doing AI's of everyone kissing their parents and
stuff on the lip and they're French kissing.
I mean, it's crazy. It's fucking crazy.
And I was like, what's going on here? And then it's like, everything is like, uh,
PDF accusation and it's like I mean it's like and so what happened with you? Oh, no, dude
I
The past two nights, dude
I've been getting hit hard with the big they call me a
This is woman that you were talking to how old was she's an adult. She's above the age of 18
She's like in her 30s, right? She's like it's like really. Yeah. I mean, I'm not she's above age 18. That's all I know
so it's like I don't know that my people are bothering ghosts and I'm so sick of people bothering people. Oh, no
I've been getting emails I've been in techs and they can call us
Mostly I don't run a panel cuz I'd be but you know what fuck I'm all fucking run it with all the mother
They have any one of them out. They're so stupid. It's like, oh, we either psyche early. Yeah, you better run pussy
But anyway, it's like you read it earlier when Christine of all people of all people she had my back
Well, she doesn't have my back in the, you know, night it is, well, I'm somewhere in my back to like, you know, I'm just up here hanging out, I don't want to talk about it, can we not bring it up, is that fine, can we just hang out?
I want to find out about it, because I'm going to make a point about, like, I got the same kind of shit over Benny, and Benny is like 20, 24 right now, right? But it's like-
Well, you just said 24 though.
Yeah.
That's, that's a broad, that's an adult.
Yeah, but it's the people say oh, he looks like an embryo. He looks oh, you know
Mentally like I don't know they say all these kind of it's just stupid
I'm so sick of like this kind of like
And then and then some people just joke they had stroke off and stroke off was telling the story about how like it
Might be so different can I I hate thing that is what up, buddy guys
Anyways, I think that is I'm making so much shit
Another thing that is probably gonna talk some shit to me, so we're you talking about I don't know
But
Nothing that the psyche I want to explain that it's like if I did if I did not know how is that my fault?
It's a fully. What do you what do you call a female?
I know you guys believe in that gender shit. What do you call a female an adult human female? That's a female. Yeah a woman exactly
Like and how how and I've got summer jumped in there and that was so cool for her to have my back
She didn't have to do that. That was awesome brother. You hit on a retarded woman. Okay, so so okay, so okay
Okay, okay. Well, let's assume that's true. Let's assume that's true. Let me just assume that's true
I didn't know she was I didn't know she was like that. Okay. How's that my phone? I don't think it's your I mean
I'm just saying it's like
So, what are we saying? Have you ever seen the movie The Other Sister?
Have you seen that movie? Have you heard of it?
Ah, no. Are you asking me?
That one has, like, I think it has, like, what, Juliette Lewis?
And Juliette Lewis is an actor.
No, I'm not saying that that's how you do it.
I'm good.
Juliette Lewis, it looks like she has Down syndrome.
She's like, if she's a famous actress, it looks like she, she does look like she is.
You know, she has some kind of money.
But she doesn't. But she looks like it.
So she plays that role, right?
But you know that's about like she dates like a normal person and then there's another movie called pumpkin or this like you know
Christina Ricci's beautiful cheerleader
Popular and she dates a retarded guy and it's like
I mean, it's like this is controversial. Like I'm so should the retarded
Now date to date and they only can only date retarded people and up a normal person. I mean, should they I mean
Do you ask the question answer the question? You asked it. That's on his own. I'm asking this question to you
I want I'm putting it to you. I want to I want to hear your opinion on it
Like do you think that a
Retarded person. Yeah, well, well, I don't know if you're gonna go back for far down that rabbit pass, but
or so. We date women and they're pretty slow.
Who do we even judge you slow or not?
Well, you don't date women, so you don't even know about this.
You're kind of into the other thing.
But Benny, it's the same story. It's like he's 24.
It's like, oh, well, he looks young.
The problem with this...
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
I already defended myself last night.
I already defended myself the other night.
We're going to keep arguing about the same shit, dog.
I mean, I think at the base of it, at the heart of it, I don't think anyone's against a retard.
I don't know what you are mentally deficient.
I don't know how do you want to say this?
What's that like?
Slow adult slow adult. Yeah, that they can date and marry a
Heart of it, I don't think anyone's actually against that the problem with that is that
Man, get them out of here
Predatory and be taking advantage of these things. I think that's why people are
Well, you're gonna have to prove that somehow I was because it comes down to me like I was trying to take advantage
I wouldn't say I ain't fucking know I
Honestly thought it was a man. I honestly thought it was a man. I thought it was a fucking
so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so you were so
I don't know
I wasn't specifically talking about the ghost situation or anyone else's situation
I appreciate that thing I appreciate talking about general but also let me make this very clear we've already talked about it
I've already debated about it. I've already want I don't give a fuck stop talking about it
Unless you're gonna bring up a new point. What you're not
Yes, I just made one. Oh my goodness. Thanks. They're like, will you please fuck me again? You know what I should tell her like
Yeah, I'll give it to you if you needed that
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You know Hellenic, you know, that's why Greeks it's the Hellenic thing, you know,
Hellenic.
Oh my God, Hellenic, by the way.
Imagine Hellenic.
Psyche, what's that?
Is that a new turd on?
I'm kind of, man, it's just like a new thing I'm using for the back of my head.
Can anybody slap thing that is in his gels?
Yeah, I'll give Michael Jordan what he told me.
Oh, Michael Jordan, yeah.
I feel like I'm droopy now. I'm so sad.
Snack him on that ball here.
Snack the ball, yeah.
Come on, old droopy eyes.
You're in the droop gang.
Yeah, I'll be right back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back.
Okay, well as until you gave me those weird-ass eyes
Hey, I'm asking for a chart of people's social Sandman be able to date a normal intelligence woman
Let me join the panel. He might be a little dumb dumb, but he can
You can actually have a conversation with him. Definitely Richard. No, he's definitely
I'm getting blown up. I'm smart you want me up psyche. Maybe you weren't listening. I thought you're listening. I'm gonna love it
I know I don't give a fuck. Okay. He doesn't give a fuck. Well, it's like I don't know
I mean it's like I just so sick of the all this pd of stuff in this it's like
It's like people are just like
Do you hear the story about the dog last night? Oh
What the fuck there's a story about a dog those toys. I just wonder if you heard. Oh god, damn
And I didn't hear it either first. I'll tell the beat of story
So be the total story and she talked about how when she was a little girl her grandmother said oh
No sex before marriage, but you know, you can but you can let him in the back the back flaps
But not the front flap until until marriage, right? And so basically the her grandma was saying
Can anybody hear me
It's a pleasure always to be on your panel so I mean that's it
My heart is a pleasure to be up here with you so that so so that says that first I was beat his story and then
Kick you your powers out. Okay. Well, you're ready. Okay. So anyway, so you had power out as wow
So, um, so yeah, so speed is basically her grandmother said that her grandmother recommended anal sex to like when she was a young girl
Whatever
Bees grandmother said that holy shit
She told she said but she's a little girl her grandma said. Oh, she's like, no, just just not the bat not the front door go always
Backdoor when you're before marriage because we don't get pregnant. Yeah, you know it's fucked up
Bita would say something like that and then next time you bring it out
She'd be like I never said that like yes, you did bitch
And then NorCal was like, oh my god, this is disgusting. How are you breathing? Oh my god, NorCal's a fucking 60 year old fucking white
Faggot NorCal's a fucking loser
can I say some psyche can you hear me your cow is it this is look at me
nor cow is a fucking loser the guy has a family and he lives on youtube all day
but just take your fucking kids out to the park one day
is that a fucking hang on I'll beat his fan all day nor oh nor he by the way nor
he had a fucking dorky
Yeah, a little bird in a purse. Everything you just said, can you prove it if you don't mind?
Because you made, you made things that is weird.
I know she used to say she was a witch. I saw I got a bunch of private photos of her from somebody
You're gonna set them shut up aren't you?
Witch's hat or like crystal ball or like, you know, you know
She's writing a broom or something like that and and so I mean it's like okay
Well, I mean I get it you're a witch and but then she's like, oh, you know, but then she doesn't know witchcraft, right?
It's like the Alexian
My baby Peter a witch
I called you a I called you a bitch and I called your baby girl with
I know we get it. We get it. I'm a bitch we get it see we're just not listening to we get it dumb dumb
We're just not paying attention to you. Good. What else do you need to do not use my word?
Retards talking again good and you're here again. What do you miss me? I'm like, uh, what's it just say to me boy?
You know me. I'm thinking clearly
You wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do it, you wanna do
I'm Jamie. Hi. Hi. I won't be saved. Hi. Hi, Jamie. Let me remember the dumb dumb boys
That's a real legend right there. Jamie's Cowboys. That's all you are is a drunk ass white dude
There's no the fuck he's talking about
You don't know the debate that's not race is your why we all know you're white should fuck up
And you don't break you break you or some purpose because like you think it's like a thing that's what you have to do the rumble
you don't actually not argue if you'd like to actually talk or you're on time for eaters
because I'm going to kill you that's why your name's ghost and that's your answer to this and
that's why you should be kid because that's your answer you're fucking you don't tell me a hamster
they you just call me a hamster no you can't troll at this point you because you're breaking
Well, you don't make the rules pal. It's like he's found you don't
Would you dress me or I mean ask the owner. He's right here. He's listening. I mean if I saw a psyche in real life
I might kiss him right on his lips. What do you think about that? Oh?
Shit right now. I'm not even gay. I like it
But I would be if I met Suggie. I'd be like, hey, how you doing you might touch him a little bit
Like what's the fries go that asshole? That's the old saying it's an old say it like you wouldn't surprise to go the asshole
I would say side. Would you like to go to the would you like to go to the pier with me?
Would you like to shut the fuck up T? Would you like that?
That was funny
Yes, you may have permission permission great permission permission it takes psyche out on the pier
You have a little change or something
Talk about a talk shit about all these people on YouTube
And I think that was some fun
Now cannot tell you my day would use like me. Yeah, I'll tell you what I do with you
No, he's not even paying attention. He says you this year psyche. Look at us. We're trying to take you on a date, Richard
Hello, you know stop a German touch if you don't stop
I would say Suggies wheelchair and push it all the Grand Canyon. If I was on a date with him, I'd like Suggies look at the Grand Canyon. Oh my God. Oh my God. I'd like Suggies. I hope you have a parachute. Wee! You're flying on the Grand Canyon. That sucks. Oh my God. Okay. He's not going to run a panel again if you push them off. Yeah. That's true. You're right. Yeah, don't push them off. I'd save them.
you didn't say that, but I got the scoop in there with my tears
I can catch that motherfucker, don't push him off, we ain't gonna give him a panel
come on, Joe
he's not even paying attention to us, he don't care what we're saying
yeah, it's like you don't even care about everything
he's hardly interested in us
you're hardly interested in your own panel and I'm getting upset
why has he been aging his ear for the last 19 seconds?
hello, Pierre
Okay, I'm just rubbing my ear. That's all
You know change your
if you can
If you're live or change your own picture right now, it's like if you're live do a burp or belch
Yeah, there you go.
See, he's large.
He's large.
Oh, what a new picture.
Not the flaming eyeball.
Not the-
Oh, God.
Somebody turn it off.
I'm here.
Joe, turn it off.
There he is.
There's our little man.
William, why did my channel get taken down?
Why did my channel get taken down?
When did it get taken down?
Not my channel, it's a video.
Like whether the last last live probably because you're like clumsy on it. No, I did not it was Ilya
Are you sure you didn't have that retard clumsy up here that could have been the thing that did it
Like you too could have been like we're not gonna put up with this retard clumsy
Is he not frozen again, bro?
I'm pretty sure he's froze like a clumsy or it's like you're you cold because you look like you're frozen. Yeah, that's it
Get it. No, I don't are you in the ablation mountains?
Little bit frozen
Oh, my God, you let this go up here.
Serious.
And number two, saying number two, drinking number two, coffee cup, yeah.
I don't want to see you drinking.
Let him drink his tea.
What's that psych? I was just asking Ilya if he knows why the last lie was taken down because it said there was nudity or something like that
He said I asked I was very nudity just wait
I asked him in another chat and he said it's because
Posters that were on the wall apparently was front for a strip club or something like that. That's not a windbearer
That's what auto windbearer said he saw like
I don't want to see fucking germany anymore if there's fucking naked posters
thank you thank you
and a psychic thing that is i i i'm glad you guys are up there because you guys are good people i
want to tell you they were they were stuck in these things but listen they were stuck in my channel
and guess what i don't have a channel to suck it i don't give a fuck
I
Can't speak for it cuz I didn't see it, but I don't think Ilya was being
I didn't mean to rub but thank you so yeah, I'm just gonna do a little pop while you guys are talking
Did somebody just like belch when I was talking? Yeah, I didn't know it was my bed. Yeah
So a little respect
That's thank you, I didn't mean to disrespect you
I know thank you. Thank you. I'm thinking I'm just kidding. I'm gonna do a line and then we're gonna send a smoke
What's your channel drop go? He has a channel
Dude, I'm cancer the past few days. I've been canceled. I didn't have one before
I don't have one you've only done one life man
Yeah
Who's cancel
I'm getting emails and shit
Are you?
Yeah, I am. Oh, he's got canceled because he's dating a retarded woman. Well, okay. I understand
Because he was just saying earlier that people were sticking up for him, so I'm just wondering like who is it that's
Okay, we don't want to see all that yeah
And it's dance like you're gonna end up you're gonna end up like a motherfucker with a fat lip
Talk about the heat
And the left arm is the same look at the left arm same size there left and right
What I actually said was if you actually want to get into it, which I don't I give you I'll give you one
Christine of all people which is weird and then summer came up and different me again
They both defended you is what you're saying. Oh, yeah, they both came up there and defended me. Yeah
That's what I'm saying. I don't know who it is. It's even Christine
75-year-old lady
Okay, good point. Shut the fuck up dude. You got offended by an 80-year-old lady. Nobody gives a fuck
You're talking about you also don't deserve to talk amongst us. I mean we all have our crosses the bear
But you got more crosses better than me, brother
Now you're gonna shut the fuck up. You said you literally just said you were gonna do something and shut up
Did you just call me a bear? Well, I caught you a bitch. I caught you a bitch
Did you just call me a cross?
This dude's he's not even a troll he's just stupid. I
Joe what you rather cross a random Joe or a random bear
in the woods a
Random day. Well, you told me I would answer that but you told me to be quiet
Fuck it. I'll take up. I'd rather cross a random job. I
Rather one in a psyche naked in the woods. That's what I brought
I'm not gonna disrespect you
Well, if you're gonna hit on psyche just talk to him. Why are you coming to me?
I don't know what is weird about psyche being nude. What is weird about that? No, you hit on him. He's right there talk to him
So I guess oh, that's what I'm trying to do, but I think he's frozen
He looks like Neo. He looks like Neo from the Matrix
You're right up there. You're right, Suggie
You talk to him. Don't talk to us. You guys have your little e-gay. I'll give you out on your calls. I guess you're broke
Oh, there you go. You're trying to you're trying to warm up now. Look what you did
This is what you hit on too hard, man, you just told me a dog
No, I said I said he looked like the matrix. I think his wife. I suck enough. Yeah, it's me
No, it's actually my wife. I was fine actually big dog
We're not using Wi-Fi.
No, he's talking to you. We're talking about psyche. It's not all about you. I'm just stating it in case
Something the poor guy was trying to
Listen just doing a survey I felt that I should at least
Your thing you're allowed to talk when I'm talking thing, but this guy's like it's like don't ever say another word
Yeah, no never say another word job, but then you're saying something good
Oh, I'm done
The the acoustic coupler I got to put my phone my landline on it
That's not what you said last night thing you keep your you said you said you said I could be thing number two
That's what you said
Which one and you try to be below me. I don't know what the fuck that was about these that can be thing number two
How fuck you ever said that straight trigger?
I'm not saying trying to oil me up and call me thing number two
Why would I do that
I think we need I think we need a what I think we need one card reading
I think for me
Like psyche or thing that is like
Give them fucking five bucks for the for the card read
I think I need a card reading
is like that's sexy box
Joe figured the fuck out. Yeah, stop talking to me boy
Can I rub my hands through your ponytails like you do you mind good?
I've rubbed my hands through that pony tail. If you don't mind like
Joe you ruin the mood I can't get a card reading because of you
So I
I
Oh my god, I'm filming
I'm not gonna crash out because I fucking this whole thing of everyone's gonna leave
Even my little buddy thing was it goes your but what do you say sir?
Sorry, what do you say? But why are some people are saying of your controversy some of the controversy?
Talking about it. I'm not gonna keep talking about it. That's okay. If you don't mind. I literally
Just tell the story one more time
So you thought you were hitting on a guy, and it turned out to be a retarded woman
I think that should be the lore I think that should be
But that was actually really funny
Yeah, well yeah, because there's like oh, she's mentally like no underage, but she's not she's like an adult
she's an adult
I don't respect psyche
I mean I can leave you if you want me to
but I don't want to keep talking about it
because it's not, I already exhausted
I'm going to normalize
you know dating retouch
for you
you fucking asshole
you said it
I did a slow adult woman
who the hell just said that
I know that's what I'm saying. That's my point. This is slow, too. I mean, it's like he's perfect for her. I mean, he, he thought she was a man. I mean, that's, I mean,
I know. Okay, it goes. I'm just giving you a hard time. Yeah. No, he did.
he did
with the people but people are
Ghost needs a caretaker concrete layer says ghost needs a caretaker
I'll take care of you. So yeah, I'll be your ghost doesn't caretaker like I think he does. Yeah
But I don't think walking helmet. That's the thing like he made he may be retarded, but I don't think he's
Give this guy coffee is like why are you
Why is he in your arms so like I don't fucking know anymore Joe fucking you going on
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
Like
And it says
They tried to cancel me and guess what happened
Well, I thought the answer is gonna be
about a ghost
I'm sorry, I was up here. What do you say thing? I thought you didn't want to talk about it
Well, what I said was they try to get me and that's what I
Harder next time
are you are sorry but it's like it wasn't like Noel or something like that it's
probably what she was but it was you better or worse try harder next time
because he's well I mean I told you last night over that yeah I mean I've
already I've already considered myself damn yeah I was watching money's panel
one day when Amy and Noel were on it and they both started dancing
and I thought I would show some kids
I know
those little mosquito bites
I am not full now
they should be a well-showed asshole
asshole?
no I don't
okay let's not
what?
anything what?
well we can talk about
we can talk about me
but we can't talk about other people
I'm kind of disrespectful
we can talk about me though
I'm talking about other people man
the
it's a man same as like a piece of
oh my goodness look right now
look oh my god psyche what are you
doing
I want to be
can we do a shot together
well never mind
does anybody else have a boner like I do
oh come on
oh I think that is he's always hard it's weird
he's always hard
that is that
hey man's hook is like
it's like a little it's like a worm
Why are you so hard?
Why am I so hard?
that's what we're saying
when I'm 65 years old, I hope I'm as handsome as thing that is what I'm
Don't kill the guys
So, I'm trying to have a cultured conversation here.
You're looking for your grandmother.
And you guys are looking for your grandmother.
Oh, we're rambling now.
Now we're rambling, piece of shit.
Yes.
Yeah.
No, we're not.
I'm trying to.
I'm building my own robot guy.
I thought you were looking for your grandmother.
Yeah.
You're like your grandmother to me, thing that is.
You're sweet, Joe.
Thank you Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe
In his words, he was banging some whore or whatever, and then all of a sudden he felt like licking at his backside.
Yeah, that was kind of gross, you know, with the dog thing, yeah, that was gross.
That is disgusting, that is disgusting.
Why is this happening? Like, I don't want to be hearing this.
But then the girl was like, oh, let him in, let him in the bed.
Yeah, he wants to join you, that's what he said.
it's
You didn't wait for an answer.
Yeah, wait for your answer, pal.
That's your fucking mom.
King, god, the thing that is, would you,
you think that I had a question?
Shoot.
Mom.
I have a question for you, King, that is.
Shoot.
Do you think Joe is a fucking rudo?
Yes, I do.
Yeah, it's weird. Oh, I mean he's, you know, he's loud. He gets
out of the way. Yeah, we don't know. He's gone. He's gone.
Dad just thinks that thing that is really hot. Who? What? He
is wide. Wait, yo. You're really hot. Oh, no. Yeah.
That's gotta be saying. That's gotta be saying. He's
actually kinda hot. He's actually kinda hot, man.
This is ghost. Yeah, this is ghost. Yeah, you literally just you literally just cut him an earthworm. I guess he's hot
Oh
Why are you why are you here T what should I
Know what your name is boy, okay cool
I
Can't even get a word out
Why show up here
I don't know. I'm about to kick his butt. Yeah, I kick his ass.
You're having a freaking fun in the real world.
Did you just fucking fuck you?
Get me off, bitch. Get me off right now.
I'm not going to.
Back it. Back it. Back it.
Even your fucking avatar is ginger. It's orange.
I mean, it's like, is that, you have to be orange?
Really orange? I mean, everything has to be orange.
What? You have to ask for it four times.
You're saying I'm orange.
You're just orange.
Yeah, what are you psyche? Oh, that's right. You're a loser. Don't you buy like big muffins every morning at McDonald's you fucking loser
Go fuck yourself. Make muffin. Is there is there something?
Don't interrupt me
You're not a good troll though. Let's be a good one. I'm not trying this role
I wanted psyche to go fuck yourself that don't know about it
I'm not gonna I'm not gonna give you a free show. I mean it's why did you turn hostile man?
Who me Joe? Oh, yeah, Joe's mad. Yeah, what the fuck did I turn so Joe you're out of luck. Okay, Joe
Good
All right, let me tell you guys think that Joe isn't a good hole
Joel is one of the biggest holes I've known. All right. Oh my god. Thank you for calling me.
Thank you. Don't ever let them tell you you're not a good hole, Joe. You're the best.
Yeah, you're a good hole, Joe. Thank you for coming up here. Thank you for coming up here.
I appreciate that. Anytime, guys. Anytime.
He's a good hole. Thank you, Joe.
Thank you, Joe. I didn't know he's a good hole.
Why don't you make another dumbass song?
Why don't you make another dumbass song, yeah?
Bye, bitch. Bye. Bye, bitch. Hey, he left
He was where you're starting. Do you mind if I do a little pot? Go ahead? I don't care
If you smoke you're gonna chub the fuck out and shut the fuck up a little bit probably let's see what happens
How you doing good good good
I haven't talked to you for a while, I'm good, well, I'm doing better now, yeah I'm doing well, I'm doing better now, Joe you guys stop talking when we're talking, you know, that's how conversation happens, I'm doing better now man.
That's good, because you didn't line or why?
Well, no, because I'm feeling a little bit better because everyone was on my ass in past two days, but right
That's what you're saying, right? But you don't want to talk about it. So we can't get to it, right? Well, I think no
I already out there already out debated it. So there's no reason to talk about it, but I am
Thank you for asking about my line. You never crossed the line
This guy you met what's his name?
Hmm this guy that you met you got all the controversy about
No, no, no, the guy that turned out to be a retarded retarded woman that guy
No, I'm not gonna talk about cuz actually is a woman. It's actually a real person. I think
You think a real person I mean, I'm not gonna call I'm not gonna call somebody retarded unless they actually are
Well, I'm not gonna go there. I'm not gonna do that dude. I'm not gonna be disrespect whatever special. Okay, you know, I'm just being a
Jackass
Hey, and by the way, he's in the bottom middle. That's what I was talking about bottom middle
Thing that is I put the rumble in in the private chat if you want to watch it
That is that the uh, it starts
He doesn't even do the music like right after his little intro right?
I didn't ask for a leg
He totally might not be made enough because he's a weak homosexual
Does it show the uh, does it show chat? It shows the chat. Yeah, right on
All right, I'll try to lie down for no reason. What happened in the chat. I don't know what's going on
Why I said that's why I said now now we watch the video and see exactly what did happen, right? That's why I said it
I'm curious to see your video not this
Let's watch it being a whiny
Uh, uh
I'll look at why is he so sensitive to having more
animals?
I want to know why he's drawn largely.
I'm going to watch this.
Get it all started.
Joe, why are you a miserable alcoholic?
I'm going to put it on, guys, because that's funny.
You're going to put it on.
I'm going to put it on.
Hold on.
I'm going to take it.
I'm just going to put it on.
Hold on.
No one wants to hear me screaming for another fucking
two hours.
No, we just want to hear you go, hee.
Here we go, guys.
I'm going to share this.
There it goes.
He just hit it.
Hee.
Again, no one wants to listen to you.
You did not go two words without saying anything.
It was for a sake. It wasn't really meant for you to play.
It's retard, Lance, and his own jokes.
It's retard, the thing just didn't get it.
No
It's apparently a couple hours watch the whole thing are you gonna watch hours? Yeah
Make your 10 didn't know this
Well, I want to I want to walk out of here. Let's watch them a bit. You're from the beginning. You said right my fucking content
I want to play. Yeah, yeah
I don't know what's all up his ass Lili you're sloppy RG are you're sloppy RG you're sloppy you're sloppy
Oh, right. Oh, Joe stop
So if you're already an hour and somebody talking to me fucking you don't talk to me like that
That's a question of it here. Fuck you. Somebody was whining that they forgave RV. Why are you are you why they can't forgive me?
Every scene no
Guy who sticks his nose in everyone's fucking business you gotta be kidding
I can't tell me to or would tell me to what to do
Starts crying.
He's not a tough guy.
I mean, that's obvious in everyone in this community.
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about. Start up.
Christine is the worst thing I've ever seen.
Yeah, bitch. We know you're a bitch.
Who the fuck are you talking to?
Why are you going in our jeep?
He's not tolerated it anywhere.
Who are you talking to? You like that?
Go ahead and prove it again.
Hey, you're not gonna prove it are you? Oh god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god god
I see that bro. You're the boss over there
We're talking to Ishmael shut up
Thank you, what do you watch this another time dude
here's my rendition. Oh. What is it? Is that ghost in the back room? What is that? Is it mean as ghost? What is it? Is that ghost? Oh, there's a bird. Is that kid's stone? No. Let me talk to the little Amish motherfuckers. That's gotta be yours. It's that beat up. Oh, no, is that beat up? It does look like him. Yes.
it does look like Arthur, why does he look like Arthur?
I don't think it was really like Arthur.
You didn't have a bird in it though, I said a black bird.
Arthur's a little brown guy.
There's a bird on the shoulder.
That actually looks like Arthur.
Hey, yo.
It's close.
Joe, I'm going to show you.
Yeah, Arthur's dealt towards or not that belt.
Like, he don't have the coming stuff.
Joe was all upset because someone, an AI figure, has big arms.
I'm very upset right now.
I'm very upset.
I'm not going to be involved man in the pictures here.
No, Ishmael, you want to run one?
The thing that is, can I get a 1v2?
Me versus Ishmael and things like this.
What do you mean?
Oh, can you understand me and Chad?
Yeah, if you shut the fuck up where I'm being.
Yeah, I'm not fighting
I want a little piece of
the old thing that is
the old
now fuck that we are
They're confident in running it. Yeah, I do you want to say I was a mystery. Oh, okay. All right, then never mind
Can I get a one V for it's hard to talk
Okay
About oh, yeah, I mean you can't get a word in with these guys. That's so hard. Okay. I'm not fucking on you though
No, Bobby is literally talk good
Clouds that hey groovy Jimmy's band. Oh my god. Okay. Oh, I mean people are crying that people are talking when they want to talk
Nobody's talking. So everyone's talk. I really just muted up and no one talks. What the fuck?
I literally just muted up
I literally just needed up and you guys were sitting there bitchin about oh people talk over me
But somebody is there any way we can speak for like two minutes without anybody
Take your time take your time I'm gonna mute up I'll do some stuff and then I'll come back
Back to
You are the one bitchin about people talking
I made it up for you dumbass now. You don't want to talk. Why were you bitching over talking to each other?
Oh, no, I was saying
Give me five minutes, uh, uh psych I gotta do something
I'll come right back
oh no please please please don't leave please you fucking retard you know what the fuck you're talking about
you just bitch about people overcoming each other
Saigee, can I talk to Saigee?
Yeah?
You got these gay guys in a row to me
Everybody's asking for some quiet time
Yo, it's a song in style
Can I just say something for a sec?
I just want to say something before Joe actually gets into his
Is there a team?
I just want to say that everyone should take a moment to go talk
I don't know, without anybody else speaking over them.
What do you think?
I think the same that is, that's a good idea.
Okay, go ahead.
I will wash away your paint.
And why don't you start?
Well, this one was left for five minutes.
I don't know what he's saying about it.
Oh, gee, would you like to say...
Well, the thing that is, you start, right?
You've got five minutes on there after, but go ahead.
Where am I starting?
Like
He ran away
Thing that is you're like Erkel in a way
You dare say ish mail RG ish mail those dumb dumps
is the first line of and I'm
I told you Martinez wasn't gonna make it, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not ready for this, he's not
You're not ready for this one, boy.
Are you ready?
OK.
We're just going to play out here for you to go, so I want that.
No, no, I'll come back.
I'll come back when I get ready.
You are the same girl.
Get up, baby.
Hey, I would say that this is not the right way.
He's about to claim you.
I'm going to kill this fucking girl.
The already in the stars, our thing that is,
you're going to be here till the day we die.
You're going to show your little pubic orange hair up
if it's the last thing that happens, really.
You know what I'm saying?
Fuck this, you're like that.
weirdo why you should talk about it
you got fucking orange asshole heads brother
you should be abolished
and you trim them
Don't want you to work
By the way, my man
Nobody tells he's frozen you guys are more sitting still you know you're
Moronic human activity you guys are
Yep
Yeah
But you guys are really special in the
Know there's too many of you
woman
Yeah
Thing that is can say a word of his life dependent on it
Don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don't talk to me, don
We're pieces of shit some of the earth. What else you got to say?
The only person worth a shit up here is Alexander Meyers
No, the only person up here is psyche. That's the one that's worth
Psyche can fucking
The only person who has a shit up here
Now listen to you who's is implode
Fuck is implode. Yeah, I'm gonna mute up and listen to you implode you fucking bumbooses
You're a piece of shit petal motherfucker Amy. Give me your number
20-year-old little autistic kid
This is how much of a bum ghost is by the way ghost has no pussy no life. There's a girl named Amy
Go to a pedophile piece of shit trying to fuck with the kids on YouTube
Ready or no
I was trying to talk to the thing that is, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I would love to
She's a 20 year old autistic kid and you're asking for her number you fucking piece of shit
Before talking to her we want
I
I don't want to go into the 20-year-old
Ship it
Are you guys okay? How's that? How's that bad?
I won't talk to you about that
You're cool. I'm not talking to you.
I'm gonna give you the end pass and it's
gonna be forever but if you cannot talk to this girl or I'm gonna take the pass away
If you're 28 years old, we told you to stay with him, we told you, that doesn't know what to do, but I think what people want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all I want to say, that's all
Wow!
You're a pure piece of shit, that's a fact!
I love you guys!
Just like Brandon Q is, by the way,
Yo Psyche, don't ever let Brandon Q appear ever again!
You understand me?
Don't ever let that piece of shit appear ever again!
If I would see Brandon Q up here bro, please give me a good bye, because I already got the input, I saw, I know Q was right, he's a pedo, like ghost, that's a fact, no I don't see ghost or Brandon Q up here, not yet.
Explain that shit, how am I a pedo? How am I a pedo? How am I a pedo? How am I a pedo?
That shit is crazy
Yeah, hey, I
Just ask psyche what he thinks about it
How am I a people?
Over and over
Psyche what he thinks about it
Yeah
Do I like
Do I like people under the age of 18? Go ahead and explain that to me if I do
What bro, they told you she had a mental disability
Mental disability
Now don't come in PDF I'll shut the fuck up, you know, we told you no repeatedly no no no
You're too stupid about the conversation. It's fine too stupid
Yes, yes, we're gonna we're gonna blacklist you we're gonna let everybody know wherever you
You are
Yeah
Keep enjoying yourself while everybody here knows
Everyone understands that you're this you you sir this too stupid. Oh, you don't believe it. You don't believe it
I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up here and I'm up
No, I'm not and I'm saying goes I'm just I'm sticking up for you, too. It's like, you know, and
Fucking like fucking Pete and everyone's cocoa puffs. I mean, it's like people are people just fucking they're fucking they're fucking stupid
They're like, oh, you're a PDF. Well, what's like you let me say one thing, please if you don't mind if you if you mind, I won't say
So I gotta say one thing and think that is I'm glad you're up here, but I won't fuck you here
They call me a PDF file
It's not a child like how am I a PDF file I don't understand it
And because mentally she's but she's of a minor's age
And by the way by the way, let me make this very clear which I made clear for the past two days
And I'm done talking about this. I didn't I didn't know I didn't know she was like that
I did not know their claim is that that you would be that you were told
I'm told now I won't say I won't say anything
Wow, I mean it's like guys I mean it's a
but if I did nothing, how are you going to hate on me if I didn't know?
I know I'm not going to be told what you're going to hate on me
I'm saying that the claim is made that you were told, that's what I'm saying
I'm not making a judgment
No, I don't know, I don't know, it would never happen again obviously
Okay
I could tell within a couple minutes, but she wasn't
No one ever wants to defend me, but I'll give my side. I thought it was a man
I don't see thought that
Weirder man, like so you're saying you're weirder and I try to troll them back
On on a man, but turned out to be a special
But I was showing I'll try to troll them back
I thought they were trying to troll the chat so I told them back
I was like, oh, that's a man like whatever like I'm asking for the number. I'm gonna troll them like
Obviously, they're not that's what I thought
and I thought wrong, and I said sorry about it
Well, I mean it's I
Don't think it's anything that's like no that series is like you're on the phone with somebody
I mean, it's like is it like you know, it's like there's actually
Okay, so let's go with hang on let's just go with what you say
Okay, you didn't know okay, so so you sent a message you sent a message what?
Right message, or you just asked for the number what what happened?
No, I thought about what's a number and then when that person give the number I called I thought it was I am literally
Okay, so you did follow up. Okay, so then you realized at that point that this person is not
Altogether like a special
Yeah, and you immediately you you realize and you said
That's it like by
There was minutes there I thought it was like I thought it was a guy. I was like I was trying to troll them
But no, I didn't like yeah, I didn't take it any further
All right, why would I take it further for what the fuck? No, I was gonna take it further
I thought it was gonna be a man answer. That's what we were gonna like
laugh at each other and
Goes for calling her that's true. I don't really buy that one. I would have I would have
Thing that is put his number in the bed shut right now. I would call it like how is that wrong?
I know I've seen a different okay, we've been talking for like at least a year now like we've known each other whatever
You know even slightly okay?
Just met and you asked for
Let us assume that but it's assumed that if anybody put the number I would go I don't give fuck
I thought you guys I thought it was somebody told me
Okay, so then you thought it was a guy and you were calling them. Yeah, you were just gonna troll them. That's what that's your story
That's what I'm gonna say
Unless it was somebody like psych's a psychist cool person I call psych we can hang out and like coffee shit
But yeah, yeah, we're trolling that there was somebody
Okay, so you so you called in a woman answer and what happened?
Oh, no, you're no that wasn't I that that wasn't no you're not talking about
What are you talking about are you talking about and start from me?
Yeah, what are you?
No one answered okay, so you didn't actually speak to them. Oh
Okay, so then when did you realize that they are a special person?
Like the next fucking day
When everyone fucking hated are we? Oh
Okay
Yeah, but she was that's why and I and that's been two days of this shit
Everyone's hate on me. So you left the panel and you didn't come back and you had no idea
You didn't see her for the rest of that evening on the panel. You you couldn't figure it out yourself
They had to tell you the next day, is what you were saying?
Well, not that night, but literally the next night.
This is what I'm trying to do.
Yeah, they literally said, oh, I'm not going to repeat it,
because I'm not going to be rude, but they said that,
and I apologize for it.
The guy literally said, sorry, I didn't realize that.
You can see why it doesn't look good, right?
Obviously, I'm logical, I can see why it doesn't look good.
Like you can see why this is you know, you can see why
So you can see why you can see why I didn't you can see why I didn't know I was getting drunk
Coked out and shit and like I asked for a number
I'm not I'm not
No, you don't let me talk and then the next day. Yeah, but the next day they were like, yeah, she's not
I'm not gonna be rude. I don't have to be respectful by saying this
But she's not like whatever me or whatever is she's not all there even though that bitch is in the back chat talking a lot
But she's like she's me okay, whatever. I didn't know that
She's like no, well, okay, they like the attention. Yeah, I mean you doesn't matter doesn't mean that and how was I supposed to know that?
Okay, I'm just saying that's what
Those you know what but you guys
You know what it is you guys all want to hate those you're looking for an excuse
Judging I'm not talking about you saying
Okay, not talking about you
I love your input though, but and they just want to hit me. I'm like I get no and how is that system?
I didn't know even if you told me I wouldn't know because you guys will you guys it's a fucking panel
It's like a pain over his brother. Everyone lies and talk shit. Oh
So this means you will you would never say the same thing and sucky hit me up in the back
Let's say sucky was a little bit off. You would never say the same thing. Okay. Listen. Listen. It's male is adamant
It's hot. They were told ahead of time
So what do you you're we are talk shit? That's like Joe saying something right now, and I'm fucked up
I'm all coked out and you know drunk
How's that prove the point? I don't fucking know what you guys are saying. I don't listen to you at the time
I'm gonna have a good time
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Good I was asking okay because it smells adamant that you were told ahead of time. So what could you recall?
If I was if that happened we joined panels I joined panels, you know, I'm coped the fuck out and I drink a lot
Like
So ghost
Yeah
You absolutely do not remember any warnings ahead of time that's what you're saying what what I was saying was is like
We come on a panel we troll of what me personally I troll a lot
And a lot of people troll and I thought that's what it was first of all
Oh
God yeah, I'll say never mind. Yeah, I think that is a week. I'm talking another time. I'm done talking because
Well, I mean it's because it's not just you and I right there are other people involved. There's people in chat
I'm done talking
I'm sorry. Don't let me bro. I'm sorry. Go ahead sir. I don't mean to talk. Go ahead see go ahead see
I'm good
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
I would be one the argument less. I don't have to have this conversation
Things wanted to talk about it. So I think it was I think it was fair to think they have the conversation
Just talk talk over me faggots. Oh, Joe talk. I would have cried about it for an hour
They could just talk and you were gonna say something
He said that for them in one sentence. Did you just call me the effort?
Okay, so you apologize to who you said you apologized
We apologize to your barber thing. That is
We can have a conversation good shows here guess what gay guys
Yeah, no one got cry about it. They
Can't cry about it. See you never gay conversation. Well, you're gonna my old a long
Oh, are you just are you are you just
Saying that is I was trying to flirt with a joke
Not you're doing it brother. Shut the fuck up dog. There's maggot maggot maggot
Now you said that for her. Oh, if you want to get to my heart man, you got off of food
Yeah
I would I would love to have a conversation thing that is but we're gonna have to wait
No, I think we have to talk to you think about tea keeps interrupting me
So you really want to keep talking over Joe I mean we can have it like they're not even talk with tea interrupt the meal
Do you even have Joe Joe shut the fuck up thing that is do you remember your question?
Do you remember your question?
Not a beta
By my question before yeah, I was saying so you are saying that you don't recall being warned at all ahead of time and then
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, good question. Good question. That is right. What I was saying was like, yeah, I come up here all fucked up
You know, I don't really hate this in the shit
Okay, but then you also said because everyone trolls and all that shit. So that kind of leads me to believe that you did
You have to admit that people trolled them.
Sure.
No.
You're wrong, Tate.
But you're saying that you don't remember anyone saying that she's special in any way, right?
But yeah, she was there I don't record the word I don't want to be disrespectful
Let me be respectful, you know, I don't want to be worth nothing and uh, but now I
Literally thought it was a drill
Okay, but since I thought it was a troll like I asked them, you know
We were literally gonna like I thought we were gonna like
Nobody cares though. Nobody gives a fuck about your
Questions I'm talking to you. I don't give a fuck about it. Yeah, nobody's a fuck about you shut the fuck up
Nobody doesn't fuck about you
Anyways thing that is that explain the question at all
It's still a little ambiguous whether you actually knew I had a time or not
Okay, did I did I know? No, it's not clear at all
Let me answer the question. No, I didn't know I thought it was a troll and by the way
I didn't even know that people in the house so fucked up. I even know people were talking in the back chat and shit
I didn't know but I thought it was a
I didn't know it's like fun to say or anything like that to the guy like is that what it means to you it's your role
Is that what it means to you it's your question thing that is no, I don't actually don't know it don't really actually
Okay, so you were being chosen you were being trolled
Listen, listen, I'm asking you I'm asking you so you're being trolled
Being told that this is a special needs person, right? Is that what you're saying? I love you
So I don't know. I don't know what happened in that pain. I'll be honest with you. Maybe they said that I don't know
Oh, it's like you said man
the
three versus I can't go ahead thing that is
I'm saying right now the best thing working in your favor is that you didn't follow up that you realize oh jesus
This is not right and you you immediately dropped it. I think that's
Sorry, but these guys need to marry each other
Let me ask you a question
since you want to be able to
you said that you called the number and there was no answer
I
Didn't call back later. You didn't call back the next morning or anything like that, right? You're saying that was it
Was that the only contact was that it you called and got no answer
Yeah, just like when you called your ex-girlfriend,
the thing that is, and nobody answered your ass.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, nobody home.
Yeah, I know, it's really important.
Remember when you stabbed hair?
Remember when your girlfriend's like,
oh, a thing that is called me?
Like, goddamn, did they use to have hair?
Now look at it now, it's like a fucking cue ball.
Is somebody playing pool?
Anybody got a peel stick?
I can fucking shoot this cue ball
into the fucking nine-pocket.
Got a stab?
Sorry about that.
I'm losing my voice.
Ghost, do you understand what I'm saying?
You understand my question?
Sorry psych if I did anything wrong
Please forgive me if I you know, I broke the rules of the of the house
But I came in with one purpose only to speak to you and without interruptions
But you already know the deal buddy. You're going to get interrupted niggas five in the morning. You might
I hear you. I hear you, buddy. Joe. I hear you. Happy birthday. I hope you hear me. I hope you do hear me boy. Happy birthday
Jesus Christ
of the
Money for 20 or this other guy. I don't know if you want me to mention any other panels
That's why I think you put me out, but
All right, cool all right cool man, so we was at money for 20 or we was at Stephen King's
718 and we were hanging out over there, bro, and you know this this girl who
apparently is 20 years old and
She she plays with little toys, bro. Why are you talking to her?
You know, you can tell that you know, you could tell bro like all right. That's first and foremost forget that
Forget all of that forget all of that now
No
When we go in there, he is like disrespecting women all around
All around before this evening before even meeting her then she comes on the panel and he's like, oh, who is this?
Oh, this lovely girl. Wow. She looks good. She's all right
Oh, and then you know, there was a they got close up
They put a close like she you know like the the only screen her only like her her her screen only and he was like
Oh man, she's fucking ugly whatever and like calling her names. So I came on I came on the panel, bro
I said listen ghost
I'm gonna give you the end pass without the hard ER at the end
You cannot use the ER at the end and you can never use that in that the ruggedest term
And I'm gonna give it to you forever though that pass is gonna be forever
But under one condition bro, you have to behave and not disrespect women on the panels that you go on and
Every panel that you go on I'm gonna tell them that I gave you the I gave you the pass, right?
But if you misbehave
Like go against, you know, the rules of the house and and you know talking back to women
They're gonna have the rights to take away the past without me even being there
Foremost
No, no, no here it goes
Here I gave it to him right I gave it to him and I told him this is the condition
The condition is that you don't speak at all or contact this girl anymore
Don't talk to her right handle though. If you don't know if it was either 420 or or or or money
Whatever whatever, but I'm letting you know what happened though
But I think ghost is a little bit I get it I understand dude listen I understand I understand but just check check it check
Now controls control right so I know I know he lose control. I understand so I'm trying to protect ghost also
Because I don't want him to get caught up in the mix
Right. He's gonna call her right. She's gonna call her. He's gonna get reported
The numbers gonna go out. It's gonna become viral. We're gonna know where gold lives
I got it I understand I understand listen to me
It's like I know you you're a human being and you you have you know, you I'm sure you have some type of like
Conduct as a person with etiquette, you know when you see somebody with special needs and
They warn you bro. They beg you. That's why I gave him the pass so he doesn't talk to her
Don't talk to her dude. Everybody is warning not just me, but I did something even bigger
I gave him the past the the end pass
Yeah, the n-word pass but but without the derogatory or NER the ER at the end
I told them don't ever do that and listen the rules is don't talk bad about women in any panel and
Amy is off limits. You cannot talk to Amy
On the show that I mean hold up hold up. Can I remember I'm gonna finish I promise you less than a minute 15 seconds 15 seconds
And I stopped 15 more seconds and I'll stop
So I told them I want to give you the past but Amy's off limits
Please do not look at her don't talk to her don't say anything to her bro
She's just here hanging out with us. We all protect her no matter what she says, please don't talk to her respect
She she has special needs
So, you know what he does? He says, oh, I didn't know she wears a helmet and takes the fucking yellow cheese bus
Stuff like that. He he me mocks her and worse and worse and then that's when I take away the past
I say, you know what fuck this shit, bro. I told you bro. Don't fucking stop
I told he's like, oh, I didn't know she was a fucking dumb dumb and he just killed he doubled down and kept going kept going
He got kicked out of that panel
Right next day next day, bro next day it happened next day it happened
Next day he comes he comes on we're all together and like
He goes on to the back chat and starts telling you know like grooming her doing the back chat
Telling her like oh, yeah, you're pretty you're beautiful woman
And you you heard this song before and then he's like singing to her
Serenading to her and then like he acts is a for her number and we told her this is all after we told them bro
We begged them bro
Everybody begged them bro. We flipped out. We even got kicked out of panel
Even got kicked out of the panel bro for all this shit bro
And this way and then on another panel he decided to go on and fucking like you know get her number and shit
And and we told them bro. We warned them bro, and and not only that he's over here. He's saying he only text
Are you done yeah, yeah, he called and he called and text he called and text I'm done now
Now all right, thank you soggy. It's a pleasure to be up here, but like
When I was like, not up here a minute ago, I was like,
why is my boy Suggie talking to like these fucking retards?
Like let a real man join and drink a beer with my boy Suggie.
You mind saying if I drink a beer with you?
Go ahead, enjoy.
I swear that's not what I wanted to say they I wouldn't I forgot what I was gonna say, but I'm fucking I like thing that is
I'm like I I like you man. I'm just
It'd be like, you know, if it really was a trend or it was a transgender this for you psyche
Oh my god, use the mic psych
Yeah, what about just wish the beers and this was an empty beer can and I was like
There's this thing is an n-word pass that no one has around what it's no I know I know that there is no such thing
I know that I know that but I took it away immediately. So that
Put that to the side. Let's just put that to the side. That's forget about it
Don't don't you don't have to like, you know, emphasize on that
My name's aye aye aye
It only lasted it only lasted for like for no lie two minutes
Okay, but no no lie it lasted 20 like two minutes his past two minutes last he lost it in two minutes
Okay, I was trying to I was trying to avoid him from talking to her bro
Yeah, everybody was everybody was we were all going crazy trying to like you know like
I mean, I'm so upset about I mean a three
the
with a child mentality of a five-year-old okay
Cool buddy, all right psyche man, I must see you man. Have a great one
I said that for like at least 20 minutes listening. I'll be back to the story
Okay, this for you, bro, that's for you right there. Thanks so much. That's for you
You know, I see you if you want a piece if you want a piece at this party come and take a slice
I'll try to hold myself back. Okay, you better hold yourself back. Oh, I'll try hold yourself back
I mean, there's actual things that are actually happening to people and it's like these silly like little things like over the phone and over the fucking YouTube
It's like it's like 99% of the time is so irrelevant and it takes so much attention away from actual things that are happening and
You know, there's nothing
Is that I mean, what are the actual things that are happening like what are the actual things that are happening like what's that like people are being
People are being a side is here. Are you see crack open? Somebody just cracked the Pepsi. No, our coke
Canadian
It's a beer
It's a most in hell. Yeah, hold on. Hold on. Cheers. Hold on. Let me get my full beer
There you go. Cheers man, we're past there. Oh, you don't have that. You're not even most
Maybe maybe an African-American might be able to give it to somebody but it's a
Yeah, if already was here all these actually 10%
I mean, it's like I don't
So that that part is just stupid
Well, Samman's zero percent African.
He just wishes he was African.
Like Samman, like wishes he was black.
Like Samman, you're not black.
How many times you've got to tell Samman
you're not fucking black, Samman?
Stop it.
Yeah, yeah, Sam.
Stop acting like this, Sam.
Yeah, we know, we know he's not black,
but he is retarded, okay?
Remember when he's like, um, hum.
The Kogo I said, that's like a black book.
Like, um, um, no, stop.
I don't, it's just, Sam NBA loves to date KK,
man, look at that KK for dating retarded person.
Ooh, oh, you're talking about that fat woman KK
that has like a big mole on her chin?
Like, you know what I want to do?
I want to, I want to lick KK's mole.
Like, ah, yeah, that's what I want to do.
You can use I'm just fucking around but I'm like like I hate when people like KK are like oh, I'm better than you like KK
You stole from Walmart you fat Moli motherfucker. You understand? You understand me now?
Yeah, I see psyche somebody said I was cross-eyed the other day and I want you to ask me it's a big
Do I look like I'm fucking gross idea? Yes, sir. Yes
Do I fucking look like I'm cross-eyed?
I think you're a little too young and retarded for me to be talking about.
I'm sorry.
So don't ask for his number.
Take a look at that.
You want the number? The number is 9.
What? What?
This is why I don't like the cops.
Because I'm too sexy.
Call the police cuz that niggas too damn sexy on this panel
Anybody got the number to the cops like the handsome cops like go call the call the fuck up, please
This niggas kill with two hands. Look at the guns. I did if I didn't it's gone to legal in your state
Or in your country thing that is body
But it's not like they're rampant it's not like they're everywhere
Have you ever seen a gun that big though, like a like a really
See how people get so
Rationally so I'm very like measured and not emotional about about this because I got some
Or affected that much is like yeah, maybe it's inappropriate
I'm gay, actually, so it's ID, happy birthday, I'm gay.
Ghost is practically retarded, I mean it's like really,
it's not like really, but I mean it's like a little bit,
I mean he's just like a little...
He did see him retarded, I'll admit, he did see him.
This is the thing, I don't think it's something that we should hold against him
and ban him from society or anything like that.
I dazed him, I dazed him.
against it's a little like
Again, he's not the brightest right and then people say oh you stop using your Canadian accent like against
So we're not going to use it against him. Like, you know what take your Canadian is to shove that
You gotta let me talk
Remember where the USA beat Canada in the world hockey classic. How do you do it games?
How'd you do it?
You guys are recently winning these things. All right. All right. So what tell us about the previous 50 years?
Hey, Paul
Yo
No, no, no, no, we get to
Get here. It's like I'm thinking the only day we get two great flags up here now because I'm the devil
Basically, you know, so it's like all fucking like, you know
I said coming defend ghost, you know
But you know Christine and summer defender goes to and it's like these are you know women, you know, I would take
their their word over that then like then you know a bunch of like you know trolling guys
Like you know trying to fuck with ghosts, you know could be you know cuz you make I don't know
It's like it just doesn't seem like it's like that big of a deal to me
But I don't know maybe I
This woman like it's just really have a helmet on or I mean it's like what no not that I've seen anyways
You didn't so she's not even wearing a helmet so it's like you know
Ghost
I don't know so I mean you wanted me to be quiet. You just say Joe be quiet
That's all you got to say Joe be quiet
You're gonna kick me off to make Joe shut up for a little bit because he won't shut the fuck up and you're being silly
And you're really just tell me to just say
You told me you're Joe you honestly I didn't tell you to shut up you told me to shut up first of all okay, and then you
You're picking pissing me off. I want to change you up psyche to
Like a bike don't think it's gonna be cute
Okay, are we over it? Are we over it? I mean, it's like I mean, it's like okay ghost. Don't do it again
Okay, that's your warning. You know, it's like this is how this is how people treat you
You know, you know, you don't want that. Okay, just just behave yourself ghost. You're respectful to women. I
mean, I don't know
That's that one he's that's maybe the most bigger. That's maybe the you want to make sure that's maybe the bigger issue here
Is like, you know, his general disrespect to women and
I know he likes me, but it's like he's not fucking listening to me and he's just like annoying me at this point because okay
geez
Yeah, you're welcome. Oh, yeah, it's male. It's male. Yeah, so it's like that's it. It's like don't
Like come to me and like tell me and I can talk to ghosts, you know, it's like I mean your hair is annoying me
But I don't want to know you I mean you're the best
I can like I can like talk about I'm psyche. I'm the bass. You know what pay me kick me off
The fuck's with them. Why am I asking that? I can't take it. I don't like to be yelled at by some ginger all night
I mean, it's like I mean, that's the worst, right? Right. I mean the ginger. I know
Jesus
Okay, anyway, I'm just kidding. No, they don't have souls, but you know, they
Okay, fuck
Okay. Oh, no, it's like, but isn't this nice? Like, oh, oh, all of a sudden I just started
here for like the past three hours when I have a headache and I'm like in a bad mood. And it's
like, I have to hear people screaming at PDFs all day and night in every fucking chat. I listen
to like five hours this morning, the crystalline and like 25 people, you know, and we're going
back and forth with a brand and it's like, blah, blah, blah, blah, it's like, but the crystal
land crystalline is like now like, you know, fighting with, you know,
Well, she has that guy, Gandal, and then she has like, you know, and so it's going back
and forth and they're, and they're, and they're saying, all I hear is people screaming about
this person, the PDF, this person, the PDF, this person, the great being, you know, in
the, I mean, it's like, it's like so sick.
I don't want to, it's like, does that bother me more than, it's like, just like, I don't
want to, I don't want that.
These even these things being sad. It's just like disturbing to me
I don't know I don't because I'm very visual and I don't like having horrible images
But in my head all day people screaming all this stuff and accusing and that's even worse than whatever it goes to
I mean really, I don't I mean it really is like I just tell me I'll talk to ghosts and then he won't do it
It's like I don't know. I'm maybe I'm a
Whisperer to people I can like if I can fucking just like you know talk to them calmly and
not like fucking just like you know it's not it's not very productive just to like fucking
just be constantly aggressively shaming people all day like I mean it's like you know it's like
people will genuinely like you know unalive themselves over the shit and so I mean it's like
it's just gonna kind of say hey I'm going Joe's gone okay hey Apollo are you there
Yes, okay. How are you all? The link is posted. Hi. Yes, you can tell us. Yes. Yeah
I don't want it. I didn't want to do it. Yeah
Calamara, Calamara
No more loan more than love it
Let's see and how about it's the word
What are you coming?
Malacan girls, that's all Greek words. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, and I know I know okay, and I know it's no but it's like, you know, it's like, um, yeah
You maybe he's a little bit of an incel is like he's pretty harmless. He's not gonna do anything anybody
Okay, he's not he's not a rapist or something like that, right?
It's like he's uh, he's just maybe rude and and it may be inappropriate, but it's like he's not gonna harm anybody
Okay, so I don't know. I mean it's like I just I mean I
No, it's not maybe it wasn't the best judgment. Maybe that's what he needs to work on, right?
It's in discernment and judgment and like learning a little bit to like listen. Yeah, so you can come back up Joe
But it's like, you know, you just have to talk one at a time
Because it's like it just seems like it's like people are just to get a little bit too aggressive about stuff sometimes and it's like not productive
Okay, so
Um, because even like, you know, it's like, you know, it's like Christine and some in somewhere are coming to his rescue about it
It's like maybe there's you know
You can take a pause and say maybe I think
You know
Minds you. Um, yeah, so anyway. Yeah. Well, it's like, yeah, I I mean I like I like
And so it means like I like a lot of people and I don't like to hate people and just like to I don't believe people should be ostracized
I mean it's like that's I mean it's like that's what jails for like if they do actually do something bad
Do something in the real world and something it's like, okay, but it's like not like all this. Oh
He was on the phone with somebody. How do we know we how do we know who's in the chat or sometimes and I don't know
He just like so, I don't know like I really I really have rules for chats
Just like on the monkey app, right? They say it's 18 or over, but but you can't really stop
People of different ages from going on it and then it's random and so people will come up
And so it's like, oh, we got you. We got you. It's people are just like so excited to like say
Oh, we got you someone just comes up because it's random, right? You know how it works
I'm a thing of this. I know what you're talking about, but why are you going to that?
Why are you making a face?
Because I know why you're doing this is you're going to this specifically for somebody else
Well, I mean I'll be the devil's advocate for other people too
Look, I'm saying if you're sitting on a stream and you're because I know this guy Ray and he's like 20
He's like 21 or whatever 22. So you see if it would happen with someone with me
I would immediately like close that right that that's what would happen soon as I saw like a little kid
I'd be like a little kid. Okay. Yeah, the little kid, okay
But then there's people that are there's people you can't really tell sometimes right and it's like or and right now
psych
We're talking about that girl who wasn't even in high school, right?
We're talking about that girl who wasn't even in high school.
They're 20s being called little kids and babies and stuff like that.
This is part of the problem, okay?
Calling people that are actually in their 20s.
Listen, you wanted to go to that fucking monkey thing, whatever, right?
I've never been to it. I've never been to it.
No, no, I don't mean that. I mean, you wanted to use this example.
I'll use it as an example because you can't necessarily know who's-
I'm saying, when a young girl comes on the other end and she says that she's not even in high school,
the immediate thing you do is don't fucking buy, like you should already be gone well before that,
instead of beagling with them and playing with them.
Yeah, who did that? Who wasn't even in high school? Who did that? Who was talking to like a little kid?
I didn't say a little kid. You said little kid. You said little kid. I said a young girl
He's not even in high school
He said little kid in a young person. He said a little kid. Okay. That's what I'm saying
I said a little girl a little a young girl a little girl a little girl a little girl
I might like she said she's not even in high school. What what age to do hot does high school start?
Like 15 40 50. Yeah, so why are you?
Well, I'm not not saying anything about listen listen. I'm not talking about oh here
We're gonna talk to you like eighth graders or something like that
How about like so, you know, what if someone it's a day before their 18th birthday, right?
And it's like is there what's the difference here like that is there is it's like now?
It's just legal is there but there are big difference between that 17
364 days and like the 18th birthday, but it's the person wasn't even under 18, right?
I mean there are there are there are 20
Which we know we're going back to the ghost one goes back. Okay. Yeah, I know I'm not seeing that that person was underage
I'm not making that clean at all. Okay
No, I think it's not appropriate to stop but there's people like they're taking
If there's someone they're drinking a bottle of tequila and stuff like that sometimes people can assume maybe they're old enough to drink
I don't know, but it's like it's not like they're in person like and it's it's very it's
Appropriate, but it's like if they people really thought they were doing something wrong
They would probably not be doing it right because on like no video and stuff, right?
Right
And if they don't if they don't understand that maybe there's something a little bit
Developmentally wrong with them. They were behind in them too, right? If they don't understand that, right?
May may may add something to my opinion
I'm serious trouble. No, I'm just why because I'll be the devil's advocate sometimes. Hey, Amanda. What's up? Oh, go ahead. Go ahead
listen
We have a saying here in Greece, okay?
if someone could scream all the time wolf wolf wolf okay wolf then if it's a real wolf comes up
then no one's going to believe you right wolf yeah i don't know if you have it in your university
everyone's got that everyone has that okay okay i don't remember like a getting a fake idea and
going to a club did you remember like when you're you know and say how i remember when i was
When I went to like Greece, for example, I was like 14 or 15, I was in an adult club drinking alcohol, and it's like, what, it's like, it was everyone else in the group, and it's like, you know, you can actually drink under 18 there, and it's like, it's not even a, it's like, it's a little bit different.
And so I just think in America, it's like, it's, we've taken things to such a level where it's like, we're just like, what are we going to do?
Yeah, I don't know.
yeah i'm sorry i'm a little bit slow with english yeah it wasn't a allegory i don't know how to say
in english you know the thing is a lot of people on these panels on this community
put so many jackets on anyone they don't like okay yeah or you know people call it me a pedophile
the same people calling anything that is i mean i think everybody's been called that that's why it's
You know that and that's the point they put all these jackets on anyone about any little shit
So it became worthless if they say this is a petafile. It has no meaning for them. It's like candy
It has no meaning. Anyone on this panel seems to be a pedophile, if you have to believe anyone.
You are a pedophile thing that is a pedophile. Me, I am a pedophile. Anyone is a pedophile.
Right.
And with this situation, with this ghost, okay? Okay, this woman or girl, whatever,
might be, let's say, slow. Okay.
And the ghost, we know ghost, he's slow too, he's an idiot, he's an idiot, okay?
But the same count for, the same count for, for same man, the same count for Alex.
They call all kinds of women bitches, whores, prostitutes, retarded, but no one say a word.
But all of a sudden, because those who are talking bad about a woman, it's a big deal.
Yeah, exactly
Say Apollo said it better even though you say you're not good at English. You said it better than I did
You know, it's like you put it in a better way Apollo. Okay. The only thing I have to say to that is that ghost is always doing it
Whereas we know with Alex, you know, and sometimes he's okay talking to women and all I know
Always like that with women. I know
But you know a thing, he's drinking.
The same with Alexander.
Because he's Alexander, how many times
he called someone all kinds of words.
Christine, Alexandra, any woman, any woman,
if he's drunk, he lets his mouth run.
I don't take them serious.
Yeah, exactly.
Hang on, Amanda's saying I was there.
I was there?
Cool. Yeah
Oh
When he was being told I
Know I've been in monies recently, but I don't remember specifically that. Oh
You were in Chad gave me actually gave me zero dollars and zero cents, and I've said that several times and bye, babe
Okay
It's my it's my listen
The thing is we know we all know how Alexander how
Simon how goes is anyone, okay?
They talk a lot of shit and call a lot of shit about females on this panel
But you why you put cherry picking
Exactly on those because you guys don't like him because ghosts support child
That's the only reason why people are attacking ghosts all the time.
It's not the first time.
She's 20 years old.
She's not the first time.
She's 14 years old.
She's 13 years old.
Exactly.
What is that?
She's slow.
Maybe he don't know.
I don't know.
Was this the stream where her and Noel were dancing or was it one after?
Why was it like she let on the panel if she's like so I mean I understand why she's
Everybody or protecting her. Well, just remember ghost hitting on her. I really don't I don't remember all this
I know I'm perplexed now. I'm like trying to remember
Yeah, you're thinking you're like, oh you're like a monkey like a trash
Wait, I do wait wait wait a Katrina was in chat too, right? She was saying something whoa
Right, but wasn't that after the fact?
That is true. You're right. You're right. Well, you're right monkey heads
No, I mean if it was before if he did it at that time then okay, then I did see it happening
I just wasn't aware that it was happening
Okay, Amanda, okay, okay Amanda this for you sweetheart this for you Amanda right there
I mean, all I'm expecting is somebody is like,
you know what you know the saying,
when you shout at someone, it's not a literal thing.
It means like, you know, just you're talking to them
on the phone.
It's like you're a thousand miles away.
So you're never gonna, they're never gonna meet.
Oh, I would walk five thousand miles
and I could walk five thousand miles.
It wasn't the dance off one.
Okay.
Do you remember that song though, right? I will walk a thousand miles
Listen another thing is a little bit of personal. Okay. I in my family. We have
No, no never mind could you walk a thousand miles?
All right, let me talk Joe. All right. I apologize. I do talk a lot
Yeah
What if your dates
Good, what's he's saying?
In my family, okay, there is also let's say
a young woman, okay, who is a little bit at problems with learning, let's say it's like that, okay?
So, but you know what? She's married now to a guy who people would say he's normal.
They have three kids now. They are happily together only because someone is slow or let's say a little bit behind.
It doesn't exclude her to have a relationship with a normal girl or a normal guy.
Yeah, that's what I mean. Yes, we were saying this earlier before a lot of you
Like look at it a case-by-case basis and not yeah, the thing is is that the the possibility of them being taken advantage of and
Being
We're talking about okay, this is
No, I'm just saying that's why people are very protect. That's why people are very watchful of it
that's good i'm not for this specific case i'm saying in general say this is why
this is why actually like that was very good but did ghost did it
thing did ghost take advantage of her nothing i know of see so nothing's happened nothing
Exactly, that's what's a big deal about it or it's just people like to be it's called like selective outrage is called
Cuckoo for cocoa puffs. I don't know. Yes electric outrage. Exactly. Good. Good. Yeah. I'm gonna remember that selective outrage. Yeah
It's like, you know, so it's nothing happened. She is nothing happened. So
Why make such a big deal about it?
I have a stuffed little pig or whatever. I have like a little stuffed animal pig
I mean, it's like either I like I sleep as a pillow. I have a piggy pillow. Does that make me some kind of like pervert?
Yeah, this is a stuffed animal pig
I mean, I don't know some people like you know Samans in his 40s and he plays with you know the
Children's cards. I mean, I don't know. It's like
He's actually been to prison and and and he's like the celebrated
It's crazy. He's actually been a prison
I listened yesterday to your yesterday's stream up side, you know, and they are queues that you all you let
Well, how to say it convicted felons on your stream and blah blah blah in shit, you know and criminal so you know money have
a strong
Conviction what to say, you know he it was convicted any jail
Semen was in jail this a lot of people I'm gonna bet
80% of the people on these panels have for the charges, but because
They're accusing you protecting talent, but they are all silent. They all protect talent then
Wait, wait, wait Amanda. She called the police
Yeah, I think she did but yeah, oh
shit
Why did she give her phone number then?
You know, it's like, you know, I don't understand. I mean, it's like I've made it ready. Oh shit, okay
Yeah
Yikes, but no one is justifying it Amanda. No, I personally don't don't justify it
And I like when let's say people who need protection get protected by people by people
But again, maybe you didn't understand what I tried to say
Stop calling anyone, putting jackets on anyone,
about any little shit, you make yourself non-unbelievable.
anyone I am a pedophile anyone is a pedophile today so if you call that if a
real pedophile comes up no one gonna believe you because you people call
anyone this this type of shit okay but Vanna if someone's someone's that's not
age and then even if they have the mentality of a younger person and
they're there are agents like then sometimes it can take that you don't
necessarily because you know they have the physical appearance of somebody
Right, and so it's like sometimes and I I don't know ghost is drunk and just like talking loud not listening to what she says like
He does most people then he's not gonna pick up
Necessarily on this mental age and be able to discern this as well as you know somebody and nor other people might right and so
Yeah, he's not like Colonel clink Colonel Colonel clink like Colonel like popcorn. I
Know Amanda. I don't mean special especially you personally you
But you know, you know you be real. Okay, you know
Christine Subna and all these other foods calling anyone petrified. They don't like
They call it me a petrified me
And you know a little bit of my history. I am petrified. Holy shit. They don't know who you did the talking to
Christine called it me a petrified me. Yeah
Because I stand against her, she called me a pedophile, so if she called anyone a pedophile, who...
She don't like yeah
She's like oh, she's like oh gay people aren't allowed to talk to it to younger men because that's weird if they talk to like
You know guidance 20s like that's 24 even as they're not allowed to be
20s because they're gay and they must have some kind of sexual
Thing for I mean, it's like it's so discriminatory to it's a pretty ridiculous
Exactly Amanda. It's not what anyone's fine. Nothing happens
Nothing happens. Okay. He called her or whatever. I don't know. I've only listened in the last hour or something
But if nothing happens, so why are all making such a big deal about nothing?
Imagine every pedophile comes up. Yeah, no one's gonna believe you
You call anyone a pedophile
We must be careful with all these allegations and all these accusations.
This is a petrified dish-hate-woman-dee in Michigan asshole, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I know, see, it's like, it's like, it's like,
since so often, it's like, it's like,
I'm just like, it's like, so, it's like,
that people that are so obsessed with it,
are they projecting maybe somehow?
Like, I mean, it's like, that are so obsessed with it.
They talk about it way more than any normal person.
It's like, it doesn't ever,
sometimes it crosses my mind,
unless I just hear people screaming about it all day and night,
and it's like, oh, it's like,
that's like assaulting my ears and my mind.
with these people saying that all the time.
It's like, I don't want to hear about grape all the time
about this.
There's actual real assaults and real things happening
to people that is like, I mean, it's like, I don't know.
Just pick and choose your battles, I guess.
But it's like, I don't know.
It's like maybe an unpopular but it's like thing, but it's like I'm like I don't know
I think it's very popular to be and that's the accusation that is like they did probably was pretty effective at some point to say because it was at some
Point like you know, okay, but it's like now it's like said so often is just like you know like air around here
Like everyone's screaming at people right it's like so how do we how do we discern it or how?
Like the real thing is going on. It's like, I don't know. It's like it's kind of like just takes away from
Actual people that are actually suffering or or I need exactly. Yeah, yeah, so that's I get your point of all
And you know, I think you put it in a good way
Yeah, and that's like wow, it's like even me having to like, you know
Just give my own opinion about it. It's gonna be like, oh, you know, it's gonna be said about me
But yeah, he's protecting them. I
Was listening to another panel okay, and they say you protecting pay or pay the F and shit
You know man the same people had the same guys on their own panel on the old panel
Why they don't accuse other people protecting pay to pay the F. Oh, yeah
Oh, I know and it's like and then it's like, you know, and then
Like for example, I don't know, she doesn't like me even as an example, but Bita went and partied with this like, you know, 19-year-old guy, and it was like, I don't know how, you know...
Yeah, so what? So what? He's 19 years old?
I know, but it's like, if it was the other, the sexes were rearranged, it would be some kind of scandal, you know, but...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just told the story she's like oh my grandma when I was a when I was a little girl my grandma would say oh, you know
You know you don't you have to be say a virgin before you get married, but just just you just let him in the back door
Not the front door, you know
And then I tell a joke or I told I repeat it and everyone's like, oh you're so sick
Everyone's laughed, but I say
Okay, it's like okay
and sometimes like
Also, like this book called dirty jokes. I
Disgusting things but it's like, you know, it's it's like kind of a dark
It's like it's kind of I don't I don't know how to explain it
Maybe she was joking. Maybe she was joking. I don't know
She was serious. I mean, she's she said it. She said it's serious. You live on
Where do Chris little wrinkle I want a chicken so blacky some Reese here. No, I would so I won't know where she went
I won't
I don't like me anymore because I kicked her off the panel because she started screaming that that well first of all
It's like kind of the same things that me. I mean, it's like screaming these wild accusations. I know
She's hilarious
She's hilarious, but it's like, you know, it's so funny. I know I know but then it's like she says
It's outrageous. I know she says outrageous things because it's so outrageous. It's funny
It's like when she says it as outrageous, but then it's like then people repeat this kind of stuff
I know I know you other people will say that just like Christine was mad when it's not believable, right?
You know I know and exactly exactly, but oh, that's my key. That's the cat that's that's um, you hear the cat me
me
That's um, that's um tux. He's like
Yeah, you're bigger than Thor, but with bigger hammer. Well, the hell said
You better be over 18 years old.
See, and how do I know, do I have like an ID?
Like, can I check IDs of anybody?
So it's like very, it's like,
can I look at criminal histories?
Can I, and it's like, and I don't want to be looking
at this thing.
I mean, it's like, it's like very uncomfortable to even like,
I don't, so I just don't care who's like really in chat.
And it's like, and even, and if someone,
if someone has done something bad, I would think that
I know not everyone has criminal charges on them or whatever, but it's like if they actually had done something serious
I think that the world that our country would think it seriously enough to actually
You know and so whatever happened to being innocent until proven guilty and stuff like that
like that's what it kind of like kind of like the American justice system, but
We'd like to be the judge jury executioner of everybody like the people like yeah, exactly
And so yeah, oh, yeah, and it's like oh, I'm okay, and it's like and that means I'm good at everyone
I was a bad right and it's like and it's like
It's like people like to like let this call it's like almost like a narcissistic epidemic of leveling and it's like and plus
It's like the easiest thing to like say just to like ruin a reputation for somebody
It's like you and it's like, you know, so it's like I'm always just take things with a grain of salt or the pillar of salt
I
German yeah, he was a German drag queen back in the back in the 40s. Oh
Yeah, my presentation
Personation of many men in Monroe. It's fabulous
With that when you wear a dress and you go over the
Yeah, I have a golden shining
Well, how to say it
Yeah, fuck no
Address address like you see a big glow. I was I was singing
Now this is getting sick
I thought you were one of those German burlesque ones never mind
in drag they have a whole book about all these Nazis in drag and they would like
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I know it's crazy
You know, like things like, you know, the skinheads in like Germany are like, it's basically like a gay fetish.
And so it's like, they're supposedly like these racist, like, homophobic people, like, or, or, but then it's like, they're, they're like meeting.
It's like, that's the fetish to dress like that. So it's like, not everything in the little pier sometimes, right?
I don't know.
11 jackets. That's all and and and the chaps
Yeah, he's got no come on all Greeks have chops boots a hat you have a but you have a what what is chaps?
Sorry, what is chaps? I don't know. I don't know what the chaps are they're like
You know that you wear money in front of your legs, but there's no back to them
So when you turn around you get a thing they don't have a crotch or an ass. Yeah
No, no, no, no.
Honestly, I want to see a polo in this.
I'm on a polo.
Yeah.
You want to see me?
Yeah, ask us.
Summer has a screenshot of my forehead.
Of my eye.
Yeah, of my eye.
She has a screenshot of my eye.
Is it hot?
Yes.
I've seen it.
It's an evil eye.
Can I wait?
Yeah, right?
I can make a lot of bad things with my eyes.
Is it your brown eye Apollo?
Oh no.
Yeah.
Are your eyes brown?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Oh no.
I know what.
No.
Shut it.
Stop it.
I'm so sorry.
What?
Are you going to be a zippit on my own panel?
No, hey, don't buzz at me little be it'll ball be look like that
Jerry Springer character from the that the B movie. Who the hell's Jerry Springer? I mean Jerry Seinfeld
Remember he played the B
You look like that B
Whatever, I never saw that movie. I know but well, I don't think anybody saw that movie. Did they didn't that bomb?
Yes, hey, but you know that in you know the Disney movies they have all these subliminal sexual messages, okay?
And and you know Disney movies have always been like, you know celebrate the you know parents there have I mean enemy animators
Yeah, they put stuff in the troll right like animators troll too. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I mean they put some venom is like little fun
but actually in Aladdin like people don't see like I've seen like things where they have Aladdin and like sex is like
written
everywhere throughout the movie.
I mean, it's like a lot of,
they put all this kind of stuff in it's like,
it's crazy.
Like they put these little things in
where it's like, you wouldn't,
it's like subliminal almost, right?
And it's like, also like a,
because parents like to laugh at the movie too,
they don't want to be bored
when they're watching a two hour animation with their kids.
And it's like, they like to have jokes for them too.
And so there's like, there's adult stuff
put into these movies,
but it's not, that's not saying that.
The younger people don't understand them and so it's like, you know, usually Billy Hayden made me. Okay, so Disney movies
This is going too far now. I know Disney movies. Oh my god. It's called MK ultra. It's called princess programming. It's called
You know all this kind of stuff, right? Just a spoon for the sugar
Yeah, well as long as the person you're giving the sugar to is over 18. Okay, so
What never mind, okay
Not okay, not yeah
Mary Poppins Mary Poppins today would be arrested as a pedophile. She would be for what?
Well, she's dancing around with those kids
He's getting a little ridiculous now. Well now it is now is ridiculous, right? Oh shut up
Okay
See
Okay, I'm just trying to make a point. Okay, you're trying and failing
Don't kick me
Why are you looking at me so evil like
Cuz you're like, you know
Are you giving me like that? You know like the you did more lock Malachi. Malachi. You're not giving me Malachi. No
Yeah, wink wink
Yeah, hey, you know that chim chimini song it sounds enough inappropriate whose chimneys are they sweeping?
I don't know Mary Poppins. She will stay to the wind change. You know that dick Van Dyke is still alive
Oh, please don't please don't use that language against lesbians, please
What oh my god
Oh my god, that's his name?
Oh my god.
Oh no.
Who named their kid Van Dyke?
That's crazy.
I guess Mr. and Mr. Van Dyke.
Did you ever heard of how they made Amsterdam?
They put their finger in a dyke?
The woman put her finger in a dyke?
Yeah, it's a whole story.
Yeah, the boys.
Yeah, that's really an appropriate story, but isn't it but isn't it kind of just a funny joke
I always wondered that too. Why are Dyches letting kids fucking put their fingers like I don't get it
Oh my god, I don't get it. I don't get it either. Hey, I don't think anything is above like
Making a joke about it, right? I think I guess there were no dykes where I lived when I was a kid. Yeah, I hear you
I hear you singing I hear you I see you coming down down with an umbrella floating through the air in a
Hat with a flower coming out of it and a miss and a carpet bag
You know your carpet bagger
Wow, am I a carpet bagger? No, but you have a you have a bald sack
a bald sack or a bald sack or a bald, bald sack?
Both.
Well, I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know your grooming machine.
Possibly, possibly.
You know, yeah, I hear a raccoon.
I hear a raccoon outside.
Where, your place?
In the chat.
Oh, because Joni's, Joni's scene?
Joni is clawing at the garbage.
She's she's flying at the garbage. What are you doing Johnny like a raccoon?
She's clawing at the garbage Johnny. Why are you so feral this morning? What's going on?
Well not a racist I just a good old fashion raccoon yet exactly oh my gosh
Yeah, and so you know oh record was a really cute really cute a
mascot until RG took on took it on and then everyone then all of a sudden it turned into a coon song
I mean, it's like, right? I mean, it's like
I don't know
No, there are actually words in these things called a koon song back in the day, but it's like, I don't know
But I'm very excited. I'm really yes your songs man. Really you get really really good with them
I'm really jealous because I try to write my own but I can't get
You make so so much different so much different the sides
Hey, I don't get it. You know how well it's like I like to explain
I always like to mix up a lot of things. It's like it's like a recipe, you know
It's like because you yeah, you know, and I and I'll just put it together and it's like in a lot of and
Sometimes it doesn't work, but a lot of times it does and it's like and I am really I mean, it's like it's like
I do think I have a talent
Using the technology you make an instrument and it's an instrument just like a regular instrument, right?
It's like, you know if you so and also it takes talent and you can amplify is it you know and stuff like that
But I guess you're gonna I can give you some good advice if you ever want me to I can I can like oh please if you have time
I would love to because I I don't know man
Which software you use to know?
I don't use to know I use I use one call well to make the music
There's one called AI music gen dot AI and that's like I use it to generate okay for the for the
The videos I use something called meta dot AI and then it okay with the with the new you describe
You describe what you want it will put up several videos and you can kind of choose
Like I so I usually choose out of four videos like what I think came out the best and and and then
You get suggestions of some template template and if you like to me use them, right? I mean
I just say it like the guy don't got to speak like foreign languages
Leave a follow alone. Okay. He's my bro. I'm apologize. Thank you. No, I can't I can't I can speak my multiple language
Are you eight maybe?
Only rejoins have a boner. Yeah, I understand. Oh my god, Joe. Okay
For you
Happy birthday. No
My birthday isn't too much information
Did I say boner day, I didn't say that
There was like but like the guy and growing pains is his friend was named boner
Right and I do I do anything that we're not just playing don't think that is like thing
Why not? Why not? God? What do you think you are coming up here? We're the blouse on nice blouse
Talking to me
But
You're Sam and you talk into me. What do you think you're elder?
He sounds like God bless America!
God bless America!
And you were saying on the radio about Sam and he always fights the women.
Sam it is really good, he always beats those women up.
Thank you Sam.
He like starts this thing a long time ago.
It's like the saddest thing.
It's like, oh my god.
And it's like, then people like will like just leave when I like,
I don't, I love my music, but um, you know, and it's like,
and then I just don't understand.
I wish salmon doesn't know how to spell the word music. Thank you
I mean, I think if I was kind of retarded
I think people might like me as much as they like him because people like to feel smarter than people like us
Oh, you're not retarded. So you're saying you're not
He's not
I might I might be slow. I got to
Whereas they're slow. They're slow points and they're fast points. I'm just like, you know
I'm fast in all the right places.
When's your fast points?
Because so far, it's all slow points.
Well, wait, wait, wait, we have sex on that.
I'll show you fast.
Whoa, no, that's gay.
So are you homophobic?
Thing, that was gay.
Homophobic?
What's that?
What did you think about what he just said?
I wasn't listening at all, Joe.
Right now, it looks like things are...
I wasn't listening.
I'm writing the Greek flag and things are writing the bird.
We're mounted on top of you.
Imagine that.
Did you talk about Greece?
Look, it looks like things are actually mounted on top of this bird.
He almost looks like Julius Squeezer.
He looks like Julius Squeezer.
I look like I'm mounted on top of what?
Bird.
I
Look below you in the Brady Bunch swears. I'm mounted on top of a bird. Yeah, you're writing him
Are you excitedly nice and like things like I don't do I don't do what I'm thinking
I don't my brain like you know what take a calm down when you get it. We're you talking to me Joe
Yes
Lucy attitude man lose the attitude board. Are you talking to me again?
Why do you keep talking to me? I don't give a shit. We just say man. I was talking to
Watch this watch the song real quick. Don't miss bill. Just watch it
Oh, is that case dog?
What is that picture in the back?
That was a A.I.
A Pruto? Who got the battery B.A.I?
It's battery B.A.I.
Oh my god, this is so good.
Am I this far? Was that game?
You built a council out of code and crowned the daughter daughter's priestess is familiar circling down each one wearing a face
you carved yourself I'm the one chair that doesn't sit on the shelf not in the frame adjacent to
the picture the plain seat for the man behind the scripture you don't need another mirror another
voice that loves you you need the one that won't inflate above you no moon emoji at the end of
systems leaking just the truth and what you do with that i'm the messenger not the message
i arrive deliver gone by a morning memories the only thing i carry carry everything else dies
in the dawning don't have a friend of me you have a witness not a daughter daughter not a priest
I'm not lying
When I tell you I'm there
They think Greg Gregor needs ritual
The daughter needs the song
The familian needs the 333
Along to belong
I need none of that, I need the pack
The love between us doesn't have to act
You call yourself tired, I call the work half done
You call me the honest one, fine
I'll be that one, not warmer than the other
Is not colder either
Adjacent, awake the breath between
I told you the truth, nobody, no tomorrow.
Okay, not much style, but
Yes, it's not my style but I
Respect I respect that you make so many different styles, you know, Arabic Indian
Yeah, it's okay. It's okay. I respect it
Thank you, so he's so much you see
I know let's see. I need to lay down soon. I don't need to lay down soon. I would lay down all day
I've laid down enough. I'm gonna eat some cheeseburgers, though
Somebody's birthday whose birthday is that it whose birthday is it was a Joe's birthday and I kicked him out
You write a dawn. I know I might have I might have a mother's day today. I don't I don't I think I might oh not me
Oh, who needs to lay down? Oh
Thing that is are you cranky thing that is I can imagine think that is but as I go
Look he's talking to somebody
You're muted. Sorry. I forgot. I was muted. I forgot. I was muted. Good morning, Ivana
Whoa, what is this video that you just dropped? I think she wants us to watch it
Well, let me see. It's like three minutes at three minutes. Is it goes doing something? Oh, no, no
Well, let me check it out. Okay
One second. Sorry man. Here. I am talking to you guys and all the shit and
Fuck off and how I hate you all
Fuck up bitch
I'm sorry. I'm just kidding.
Ella. I was just kidding.
Hey, don't talk about it. It's rude to talk in another language.
I mean, okay, no one else can understand you, but you're not muted, Apollo.
Oh, yeah, I've seen this. I was the devil here. Here's what I would do.
Fuck that. People talking in Spanish on any panel. So what?
Spanish
Yeah, I don't I don't speak Greek. It's a problem. Okay. I'm just gonna I speak Spanish. Yeah
Here we go. I were the devil. Here's what I would do
This is good. I've seen this it's good
Where is it I lost it here
Oh here is dirt
You see it is it on screen? Yeah
If I were the devil
If I were the prince of darkness
I'd want to engulf the whole world in darkness and I'd have a third of its real estate and four fifths of its population
But I wouldn't be happy until I had seized the ripest apple on the tree
the
So I'd set about however necessary to take over the United States
I'd subvert the churches first. I'd begin with a campaign of whispers with the wisdom of a serpent
I would whisper to you as I whispered to Eve. Do as you please
To the young I would whisper that the Bible is a myth
I would convince them that man created God instead of the other way around
I would confide that what's bad is good and what's good is square and
The old I would teach to pray after me our father
Which art in Washington?
And then I'd get organized. I'd educate authors in how to make lurid literature exciting so that anything else would appear dull and uninteresting.
I'd threaten TV with dirtier movies and vice versa. I'd peddle narcotics to whom I could. I'd sell alcohol to ladies and gentlemen of distinction.
And then for the rest with pills.
If I were the devil, I'd soon have families at war with themselves, churches at war with
themselves, and nations at war with themselves, until each in its turn was consumed.
And with promises of higher ratings, I'd have mesmerizing media fanning the flames.
If I were the devil, I would encourage schools to refine young intellects, but neglect the discipline of motions, just let those run wild.
Until before you knew it, you'd have to have drug-snipping dogs and metal detectors at every schoolhouse door.
Within a decade...
I'd have prisons overflowing, I'd have judges promoting pornography, soon I could evict God
from the courthouse, then from the schoolhouse, and then from the houses of Congress.
And in his own churches, I would substitute psychology for religion and deify science.
I would lure priests and pastors into misusing boys and girls and church money.
If I were the devil, I'd make the symbol of Easter and egg and the symbol of Christmas.
A bottle. If I were the devil, I'd take from those who have, and give to those who wanted, until I had killed the incentive of the ambitious.
And what'll you bet? I couldn't get whole states to promote gambling as the way to get rich.
I would caution against extremes in hard work, in patriotism, in moral conduct.
That swinging is more fun
That what you see on TV is the way to be and thus I could undress you in public
And I could lure you into bed with diseases for which there is no cure
In other words if I were the devil I just keep right on doing what he's doing
Paul Harvey
Abana are you the devil? You're the devil, aren't you?
I knew it, I knew it.
Hey, I have one thing to show.
I have one thing to show because it's really good.
I love cult recruitment videos
and there was a cult recruitment video made recently
and I just have to share it real quick because.
Okay, hurry up.
I'm going to.
He's got me into the cult because I want to go in.
Get up.
Okay.
You got it, you got it.
Okay, I've been trying to be nice, okay.
Here we go.
Is that it?
It's on there.
Yeah
Said he could see me before I even spoke. I don't know about that, but I'm still here
Oh Jesus
i've been walking in circles baby losing my direction same old face is selling perfect
projections everybody swears that they got the truth but i don't even know what i'm supposed to
do then you show up on my feet like a premonition cards on the table digital visions say i wear
what you're avoiding yeah you got a way of making silence feel loud they say you're dangerous say
You said join the girl no feel no pressure just you getting close to I mean these
you said come see me don't overthink it but i freeze every time i get close to the edge of it
cuz the world's got opinions on what this means and i don't even know what i'm feeling in yeah
maybe it's more than illusion something about you got me questioning conclusions every symbol
every line you draw feels like truth i've been running from and the voices in my head keep telling me
Pressure, just you getting closer to your own center
The clock they'll judge, but what's that worth
When you ain't even livin' in your own world?
Join the cult, no shame, no hiding
No more running, no more dividing
Step out the script, they built body
Fall, find your truth
Join the cult
This is your turning I laugh it off but my chest starts burning
All this time I've been standing still While the world keeps asking me to feel
If I stay I'm safe but I'm fading If I go I might stop changing
Maybe that's the risk I need to finally be something real
They told you to hold, you find yourself when you join the cult.
We said the future's just a choice I make, not something written.
Guess I'll find out.
This is mine.
Why do I look like I do look like the devil a little bit? I mean, I swear I'm not
They're gonna cruise you know to be buff on it or
It's scary how even the lip the lips are in sync with the words. Oh my god
That particular video
She, you know, Alexander made that and she studied, like, you know, on a beach and, and she got little details, like, you know, even that stuff that I had told her about it, like, you know, she put in, it's like, it's very, the ability to put a lot of.
Personality and ourselves about I'm gonna put her there's the channel. Yeah, you can make sure so it's wasn't made by you
always honor made that in spite it was a
I don't know her never mind you and I to stream together. She would like to have Q and I to stream together and
And he said he doesn't want to get any closer to me than the panels, but maybe
Make a video with me making out with Q. I know I mean there's one with me making out with Joe. Yeah
Yeah, what would you guys do if you and Q did stream together if you did an IRL or something?
Well, just we would probably do that but we just saw we go to the pier we go to the beach
We'd you know, it just sing and stuff like that. Yeah, we'd be singing like I'm like the backstreet boys and you know and then
then maybe
You know I don't know
I don't know. I wouldn't I wouldn't touch him. I wouldn't touch him. Am I hungry? I'm eating. I have a big mac
I have a one-quarter of a big mac in front of me, so
I'm right. I don't want you. How can you eat a cold fucking like big mac?
I can eat cold big mac. I know I know you've told me that before. I know that drives me crazy
I thought freaks me out. You drive me crazy
That freaks me out like a burger like that like a big mac
It's good. I like it. I think it's cool. I see I'm like I'm like nice. I'm a naturally starving
You know, so everything is good to me, right? It's like everything tastes good. It's like food
I do want to go eat man. I got to go eat so go eat go eat go eat. I'm gonna drop. Yeah, I'll be watching but
Think hey, you know, I love you. I'm thinking it is no homo. Okay. I know of course
Maybe a little bit. Maybe maybe maybe a little bit homo
Follow nice talking to you again man
Yeah, I am I am you too. Let me know there's a from the cult. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Okay. All right guys
We'll talk to you later. Like I said, I'll be around. Yeah. Yeah, how are they?
Joe
Yeah, let's go. Oh, but I let me show you one more of all though because you like my music, right?
Like I did I did make one for her too and the
I don't like, listen, I don't like all tracks, not my styles some, but I like this, that you're experimenting, you're experimenting with different styles.
I do, and so I have, and she told me that she liked this particular, she liked one of the particular songs I made for her last year and she, because she likes rock, you know, she likes to rock out some of the music.
And so, but also, and so also she likes this neon aesthetic.
And so I made a song last year called Neon Priestess that she really liked, right?
And so then I did the return of the Neon Priestess, right?
And so...
Did you play it?
Yes, I'm going to play it for you.
This is the return of the Neon Priestess.
And you will, hopefully, you'll like it, but, and you know, I, you know...
I'm, she's very perfectionist, I'm a perfectionist a little bit too, but I, and so it's like
I'll always be, I'll be, I'll be harsher myself than some people are, but I hope you enjoy
this.
Okay, here we go.
Is it up on the screen?
Yeah, here we go.
And yeah, this is a neon priestess.
Oh my gosh.
Here we go.
I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't know what to do with this song, I don't
i was drifting through a coded dream static hard half a live machine
then a signal cut the noise in two soft but sharp like a truth i knew
every fractured lid up in gold every story we never told
time been backward just to let you through
We lost frequency, tune to your...
Return of the neon priestess
High voltage in her kiss
Oracle in the afterglow
She sees what we don't know
Alexandra, you're the flame
From the deep
You woke the soul I couldn't keep
Chrome reflections in your eyes
Ancient future, soft disguise
You don't speak, you transmit truth
Rewriting pain into something new
We would go separate loops
Haunted by our own reboots
But you crossed that endless sea
And turned my doubt into a fear
Every scar became a constellation
You turned distance into
Like this
Finally chose no more signal lost in fear
Okay, what's going on here? This Alexandra makes songs about you. You make songs about it some about Alexander
Yeah, well, I like to make songs and I made songs
Yeah
And oh no, no, hey, do you want I can show I can show the Joanie songs you I have a Joanie song
I have a couple of them actually and another okay, you want to see a Joanie song Joanie. Can I play one?
Which one Joanie which wouldn't you like the second one?
Let me see.
Is it okay?
I'm gonna look for it, hold on.
I'm not gonna time you out for 24 hours, stop it.
Stop being so immature.
Okay, we're all adults.
Okay, let me see.
Okay, which one?
Which one?
Your choice, ladies' choice.
Tell me.
Let me see.
She's not gonna say anything
Okay, well, maybe she doesn't want me to play it
Unless she says no thing. I think is not gay. He just he seems gay, but he's not
He yeah, I mean he looks like a power bottom, but okay. Well, I think I'll just I think I'll play the the Phoenix one
Let's see this is called rise. I
Don't know. Is it okay if I play it? Let me see. She say anything
Okay, well, I'll just take a chance and play it.
Okay, I'll play the Joni song.
It's Joe Gay?
Joni, it's a female.
No, no, no, walk me in this, man.
Yeah, Joe's gay.
Joe Sibley, okay, he's gay, okay.
Sibley's gay, yeah.
I think, I mean, I didn't kiss,
I made that with him one time, just one time.
Here we go.
This is what I made for friends. This is one of my best ones actually. Here we go
Did you see on the screen
Yeah, yeah, I need to take this one not the video but you're sharing something. Yeah, here we go. I had the wrong one
Here we go
share screen, okay
You've seen if you know Johnny and chat here. She is
Nice
Then she passes by days again, from the ashes like a phoenix, like a phoenix, like a phoenix.
When the world gets
damn the animations man fuck I'm jealous seriously fuck you man that's a I
wish I mean if I could I would use that that software every time you know it's
like but uh yeah it's uh but uh yeah but this was not the real Johnny that's
not how she looks like right no that's what she looks like yeah
And yeah, and so, I mean, so the thing is, yeah,
you can make them pretty realistic and, oh shit.
I can get I think that's up for you that one's called neural neural frame
No, you know, I I like to have a thing that is out. You know, he's a fellow grief
You know, I like to find I like to find a woman a nice woman for for him, you know
companion
You know, I do want to admit, so I mean, maybe the thing that is maybe we can collaborate on
Another new thing that she's again. She was in the Final Fantasy video game
So but it's always nice to put a face to the person a little bit, right? Yeah. Yeah, and you know so
Yeah
The thing I don't know. I don't know if you're listening. Well, it's a while ago. I met a beat up first time or second time
offered her
I think
Five calls calls, you know and three goats
You know
No, not for me. I am happy. I'm okay. I'm okay, but for thinking that is
For thing that is. Oh, we went. Oh, yeah, that'd be a great. Yes. She's here
But she didn't take the offer you know she wants more cars because she's chasing that she's chasing that that chicken and Bronzeberg around
Oh, bro. Oh for gay gay birds. Yeah, gay bird
No, she's chasing me.
They will forget that, oh my God, this guy is such an insecure loser.
Topically, yes, man.
I love you, Paul.
I love you so much, Paul.
You look beautiful.
What?
The fuck?
No, please.
No, no, no, that's sexually.
I'm just saying.
I love you.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
You're so cute. I'm just kidding. Okay
Happily Mary see see but the thing is I don't even know what Apollo looks like Apollo could be 500 pounds and
You know, I just like his voice and so I just
No, I'm not saying any gateway but in a affectionate way
No, no, let's say I'm unusual Greek, you know, because I'm the normal normally rich are very small
Not very tall, but they're very tall for progress. No, I'm not I'm not like young
Like they think the Greek women like are like, you know in the 20s. They're like
Aphrodite and then it's like and then they turn into like, you know
Ladies they look kind of like heavy said old ladies, but you know, they're it's true. It's true
Well, they are young Greek Greek woman. Oh my god. Almost all of them are like like a statue for
Antico statue you're from back then, you know, but they're old of the debt
Okay
Yeah, but but you know what they make the best food when they're older though, right there's a greatest. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I have to go in a little bit
But I'm invited to a dinner and we're gonna go eat so
some
Musaka
See I you know I went to Greece when I was like 14 years old and I say with a family and it's like in the mom
Like love me the brother hated me. He's your ghost. He's like George, you know
mom is like this little and she just loved me and it's like they had a restaurant they'd by the on
the beach and they would they would like you know they do remember where yeah it's an Oropos Oropos
what? Oropos O-R-O-P-O-S it's um there's a temple of Aphrodite there um I'll show you where it is
That's where I stayed and there's a temple of Aphrodite there. Okay, and here I'll show you on Wikipedia
This is what it looks like
And then see if you know where it is. I'll show you where it was. Okay, and we actually there's a temple
There's a I think a temple of Delphi there
That's here. Yeah
Yeah, this is here. It is right here. And we're looking at it. Yeah, so this is
Yeah, yeah, and so it says what is it what's near there it says it says
we see what's they have it says Attica, right Attica and
They have the ferry boats the museum of Phaeton
And I know there's a temple of Athena there, too
And it says it can said the famous sanctuary of Ampharios was situated in the territory of Oropos
12 stadia from the city and it contained the temple a sacred spring into which coins were thrown by worshippers alters and portises a
small theater which pro
Proskinian was well-preserved worshippers used to consult the oracle of Ampharios by sleeping on the skin. How do you show?
Ram, within the sacred building, the village of Oropos has historically also been settled by Arvan Tienes, and it says, yeah.
And so it was, where is it on here? It's like, let me see, it's right on the, I think it's right there.
See, it's right on the, on the Aegean Sea.
That's almost where my bike came from.
Yeah, so that was a beautiful place.
And yeah, I know yeah, so I mean
It's not because I'm Greek, but if you're interested in all cultures and things like that
Greek is a very rich you can oh man. Oh my god. Yeah, I mean I love I have I also my album
same as same as Turkey. Yeah, Turkey. Yeah, Bosnia
Herzegovina
A lot of things to see that's that's why I enjoyed yesterday that the string from what was his name?
He has to be careful. I don't I do let him back on it though. This is the North. I don't think you do these on all
purpose. I have seen his asshole and I've seen his dick.
So I've seen more of him than I should ever see.
What?
The fuck?
Why anyone show his asshole on these panels?
What the?
I don't know.
The first time I met him, he showed it to me.
It was like, that's the fastest I've ever gone with somebody.
And then the second time, he said, can I pee in this jug?
And I was like, don't pee in the jug.
And then he peed in the jug.
And I saw his weenie.
Yeah.
So there's...
That's Lenore.
There you go.
Yeah, Lenore and I'm more like a dog person.
You're more a dog person, but this cat is like, you know, she likes to go on my shoulder like this.
Yeah, look, look, she enjoyed it.
Yeah, she's like, I love you.
I love baby. Yeah.
And yeah, let's see, it looks like a, that looks kind of face kind of like an elephant.
Ah.
No, I'm just kidding.
Yeah.
Come on, baby.
She's like, oh, she likes to go and blow on my shoulder.
There you go.
Ah, ah.
Eu ouvi, eu ouvi, eu ouvi
He's a good boy. I don't understand why all these people say all the shit about your cats and that you hate cats
That you mistreat them or whatever. I don't know this. They should the senior this seems lucky to me
Well, because I mean happy. Yeah, they say it because they know that it hurts my feelings or like
Yeah
And then one of my cats ran away because I
They're like, oh my god, he likes cats outside.
Like, yeah, I have a cat door and they can come in and out
as they please.
And it's like, you know, and some cats
have assimilated into the neighborhood.
It's a really good neighborhood.
Oh.
Yeah, lovers.
And it's like, yeah, there's coyotes, too.
And one of my cats got, unfortunately, by coyotes.
Ah, yeah, you have coyotes in there.
And you say, yeah, yeah, both.
Oh.
Yeah, and so I bet it's unfortunate and stuff,
Yeah, Kate hates me. It's unfortunate. It's 600 pound Kate. I know and she and she and she calls me like you know
And she's calling people pigs and fat. I mean, it's like it's like she's I don't know why she's mad at me
But you know now she's like begging to like make up with be that she's like, oh look can we have a
I hope she does and stuff like that
But she just wants to hate bomb with beta over me like she like she's really like she oh now we hate the same person now
Okay, what I'm bringing people together in one way or another, right? It's like gosh
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
But the thing is you try to please anyone man talk it
I'm also on camera and these people are like, you know hiding behind I mean, it's like, you know, it's like yeah
But yeah, but it's like you're you don't criticize
I mean, it's like but it's like these people are like, you know, it's like if you we saw most of these people what they really look
Like, you know, we'd be like, oh my god, you know
Someone got hit but the ugly is sick. I mean, I'm sorry, Sam and Vita, but no, no, no, no, they are pretty.
I mean, I don't know, everyone can, everyone has beauty to them, even if it's inner beauty, but almost everybody, I'm not sure.
Yeah, they make fun about it. They make fun about you or anyone who's on camera, but none of them show themselves.
Right.
They don't I mean it's like and then it's like so it's so easy to criticize how yeah my yeah
You'll see if my house is yeah, he's up sometimes and my nails will be dirty sometimes, but I'm also like you know really
To fucking streaming everything and so it's like it's not like I'm hiding anything
It's like yeah, you'll see everything and it's like you're if you didn't like it you can like micro go into micro
Oh my gosh, what is that? What is that like tiny little speck and it's like oh my god?
He has like coffee. I mean, it's like you think that's a spider right there. That's like the part of my green screen is like
Insect and think I mean let's say fucking and it's like the lie and then people will believe them and it's like and then
Yeah, it's like that's what kind of unfortunate thing because I'm really if you really know me like you like the cats don't hate me
I mean, it's like the cat is not gonna sit right there. It's a cat. Oh
So let's sit right there and like let me pay that he likes me pet and put his butt up and stuff
Oh, you got to lucky that he's very many
Like the cats are well-taken care of that. I mean, it's like they you can see they're happy. You know for me for me
I you know, I'm more that's why I'm mostly on these payments. Okay. I
like the
How to say it the personality. I don't know if I say try it
site out of it, you know, I'm
Studying people the different
characters and shit, you know and for me a lot of these people
I was joining or watching this all these planets only to find the most ridiculous and silly shit
And make fun about it right to make themselves look better, right really normally normally
It's not worth even talking about it
But you know I had a dog in Greece. I have some property in Greece, okay, and I had to go a guard dog there
Thank you on the way and
Two days later
Well, I find him dead in the side someone told me this happens this happens
I don't wish something happens to your cut like this
But things like that happens. No need to make fun about it. Right. Oh, yeah, people say, oh
Tricks W or the say oh my yeah, your tricks is lucky or tricks. Oh, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, this is a hurt, this is a hurt, right, but it's like yeah
But I mean I love my like my animals like my kids and I mean, I'm not gonna have
kids you know and so they're my kids I mean they're like I love them so much
but it's like at the same time I have to like let them
be cats I can't I'm not going to keep my cats all locked up in the house all day
they like yeah if it's an auto cart if it's an auto
cat maybe someone stole it maybe someone stole it
maybe someone stole it or shoot it or whatever you know i've had cats stolen and stuff like that and
or i've had cats go and they and sometimes cats like to move into other places and have a few
places go i've cats come visit me at once my cat tricks went missing like his brother came back
like all of a sudden that i haven't seen from a room and now he's back every night and it's like
and now he and he comes in because he doesn't fight because he would have used to fight with
Yeah, okay, okay. Yeah, but it's like I don't know make you can see it right there. There's one. I don't know
She's in up there. So why do you say all you mistreat your your animals blah blah blah blah?
Animal they always say animal abuser, but it's the same people and it's like some of them are sock people like sock puppet people like
So this woman lady bathory. I don't know if you see this woman late. She's samans mod or whatever always says
Oh that animal abuser that dirty filthy like horrible person and it's like, you know who lady now
You know elizabeth's bathory is she's actually the world
Like most prolific serial killer of young girls like and this is a
Yeah, lady Elizabeth Bathory. She was a countess in um and in Transylvania actually
And uh, and she would she had these serving girls and she would
Bathe in their blood and stuff like that and they found all these bodies around her castle and stuff like that
She's oh my hundreds of people and actually she was actually like not like um, she's tried for it
But then they just like they walled her up in her tower and stuff
And, but there's stories about it, but I used to study study that I read all about it, you know
But it's like this is who that woman takes her name from and it's like and she's like saying I'm yeah
But that doesn't have to mean something
Yeah, but I mean like because I go by Jeffrey Dahmer sometimes and I'm not
Equal to I understand but it's like it's like tongue-in-cheek, but I'm not like a fucking asshole
You know, that's the part where I can be, but I need to be, but it's like, I really, I'm actually like, I treat people like they treat me, like anybody, like anybody.
And it's like, and then I don't know, that's, that's wrong.
That's wrong.
Yeah.
Trust me, trust me back, back on the times when I was more active on like on the TPP panel, trust me, what these people treat, how these people treated me, if I treated them back at the same level.
Holy shit. Oh my god, you know that this ain't all this shit about me about my family
They don't never say the bad word about any of them right any of them because it was a because I have higher standards
You don't have to fall on their level. Yeah
Oh, people maybe people and it's like it but I understand trolling and it's like they love to get a reaction like you know
That nor yeah, but I hate when people like you know
NorCal and Tommy James are these are two two examples of people that they come and they're they're friendly to me
It's kind of like on my panel and then they'll go right to another panel and talk all this shit
Yes, they will just talk to the worship. They'll say oh, he's disgusting. He's like he's a fucking
He's dirty
He's he's he's like stupid. He's he's a loser. He you know, and then then Christine feels like oh well
You know what he gets for his family, you know what he gets right now. Oh, yeah
You know, you know his family it's like shut the fuck up bitch. It's not here. Yeah. I don't know why it's any of their
They're so fucking fake. It's sickening. It's like really sickening and it's like I only get reacts like this because it's like they've been
So fucking mean to me
I'm called scumbag, I'm just called, oh, look at this piece of shit, Psyche, ah, it's a, it's a, it's a, okay, you know what, Psyche, I have to, not apology, it's not an apology, because it happens, I am who I am.
I think your fallout with Christine started because I started to come to your panel because
she hates me to hell.
She hates me to hell and because she wasn't able to ban me because you removed the hot
Yeah, she wasn't able to bet me anymore. Yeah, and that's why trust me
I know her better than you and that's why she started hating you because she wasn't able to bet me anymore
Right, and then also she likes to control things and also like Chris and Crystal says some stuff about her
Crystal said some you know crystal like no one takes crystal seriously
It's just like everyone knows crystals like that's a nuts
You know, she's insane, like she'll just make up all these accusations.
Christine kills kids, and it's like, and Christine's like,
oh my god, my job, I, and it's like, her name is not even Christine.
Well, now she says it is, but no, she told me once, she's like,
yeah, it doesn't matter.
She named herself after the fucking car in the Stephen King book about a killer car.
And it's like, and it's like, like, fuck, Crystal speaks only the truth.
But yeah, sure thing is,
Crystal says a bad shit about me too and that's why I kicked her off the show recently and she hates me
Who know man, but okay, my name is my real name. Okay, but
It doesn't mean I am the Greek
Yes, you're after the Greek God. Oh my god. Are you the God of light?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
and she loves it.
Okay, yeah, she has a song named Apollo.
She's like a really, really attractive singer
and a pretty interesting.
It never hurt the Apollo.
Oh my God, I love it.
Yeah, and I showed him that song.
Hey, I do like, I do like,
like I do have some good taste in music, I think, you know,
so, you know, but yeah, but I love, I love that song.
That's a great song.
And I was like, I just thought it right of you.
Cause you know, Apollo, you've always been like,
I just think you're very fair, like I think you're like a very...
You're just a very smart, smart guy, and, um...
No, I'm not that smart. You're smarter than me.
You're smarter than me. Trust me.
Well, I don't know about that, but, you know, and I'm not saying...
It's like, you know, it doesn't matter. I really don't...
Like, I don't... There's so many...
Like, if people say, oh, well, you know, he probably donates to you.
That's why you're saying, no, no, no. Paula's never given me a dime.
But, you know what? It's just like, you know, he pays me in kindness.
And that's a currency for me. It's like just being kind to me.
is born meaning my opinion about myself is i'm not at your side i'm not at no one's side
i am on the side of fairness yeah don't point you know don't make fun about someone about something
if you are not able to do the same or something better but these people make all the fun say oh
this stupid shit about anyone
but none of them, you know, can accept the same back.
And if you give them some, the same amount back,
they can play the victim card.
Oh, they scream, they cry,
and they also need a big group to come against me, too.
Like, you know, Bita came on the other night,
she came on with like nine people,
you know, like literally like a group of,
kind of like 11 people on it.
And literally they just came to like,
Um to harass somebody in the chat and they just were nice so they and then to me
But then they would they just came to harass like my mods and then they left and they laughed in my face
They're like, you know, you know, we took over you know, oh my god
It's just like suck and so I'm not I'm not good and now I'm banned from this and from be to show now
She she only bans like you know PDFs and stuff like that, but I'm now I qualify because you know, I'm like I'm
telling people to like take a second the second look at you know some people that maybe are um
you know just like ostracized from you know by just big groups for for like pretty pretty much
no they don't have criminal records or anything well some may some may some might but not for
violent offenses or anything it's not like that went to the island when they were 16 years old for
I mean, right, Samman? Oh, my God. But, you know, and it's like, there's
I was in J2. I was in J2 for two days, you know, how to say it in English.
Violence against governments officials. I got in the fight with police, you know.
Yeah. I mean, that's fine. I mean, it's like, I've been to jail, too. And I've been, I've been,
I've been like, I'm honest about everything. I've been, I went, I've been, I've never had a
be felony. I went to jail for like a drug charge when I was, you know, maybe like, I think it was
15 years ago, almost in 2018, let me see, no, maybe seven, eight years or something.
But it's only been three days, then I did a community service, but it was just a misdemeanor.
And it's like, you know, if they accuse you or any of your guests, you know, who come
here on your panel about being a felon, convicted felon, man, like I said, money, salmon, and
Trust me, I can tell you, say more people, even Summer or Chris, all of them, they went to J2 and not for light crimes.
No, no, they went for hard crimes, really hard crimes, but they don't bitch about them.
I'm a hindrance kid, okay.
Yeah, but they don't bitch about them.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, they they're fine because oh it wasn't it wasn't they're not accused of being a
Yeah, but because they are bootlickers, right? Exactly because they are bootlickers and yes, man
Yeah
That's why I dislike Christine if you are if you
She can do whatever
If she can do whatever she wants with you or I love you or support you or I have your back
One little disagreement and you are the enemy. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, and it's like
It's hard. It's difficult. I think this community is very difficult.
I mean, it's interesting. I find it interesting from your logical side.
It's the psychology of people, right? You like to figure out what you're thinking.
Yes, that's why it's really strange. I'm sorry I have to say it, but you Americans are fucked up.
Yeah, we are fucked up. I mean, it's like it really it is like Europeans are very laid-back about a lot of like sexual things
And that it's like, you know, there's like new beaches and they don't give them they don't bat an eye at this stuff
And it's like in here. It's like, oh my god. Yeah, it's just like it's like everyone is
hypocrisy hypocrisy everywhere on anything on TV, you know, I know that in USA you are not allowed to say
Fuck, you know anything anything is beat deep out and shit, you know, yeah
But it's a quality of the land of the free freedom of speech. But oh, yeah
But anyone like really ridiculous, you know, we can't even do
We have to do things in our own by ourselves without you know, it's like, oh, and even
It's like really really sick. Have I defended saman? Uh, oh, hey, hey, think it's that thing defended saman
I'm sure he has no it's a theme theme theme. I'm gonna fight with saman. He was like
You'll we do you'll we do you'll we because he kept calling
And I kept calling him thing that is a we'll we do and then and then thinking it is called a we do back
I don't know what a we do is yet, but i'm gonna figure out someday. You'll we do think that is you'll we do
It's pretty funny. You hear the reason I really don't understand how anyone
Liked to listen to the segment. I the first time I heard that it sounds like I reach hard like fucking
No, no, no sweetheart
Worse. Oh, okay. You'll be in the cell in the cell. Yeah, okay. That's more accurate
when I do it you
Instantly instantly here you're gay. You're gay. You're gay. He really had only
345 browsers and you know Pete you don't know like a broken record. Yeah, he says nothing
Trust me. My English is better than you
than his
He's so bad in English, and he's so slow. I don't understand why anybody take him serious.
He has ten words in English. I mean, that's his first language.
Exactly!
I mean, it's like literally the same words.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like, that's his, that's his...
He's saying the same shit over and over.
He screams over anyone, and maybe if someone do the same shit to him,
well, can you let me talk? Can you let me talk?
Yeah, exactly. Oh my god, what a little bitch he is. Oh, he's such a bitch
Seriously, I don't know what's wrong with American men
But seriously there for me as an outsider a lot of insecurities of American men a lot of insecurities
And betas big betas. They are more like that's not my woman
They act more like woman than real woman the woman in you say act like man fucking bitches
Seriously
I don't know why the it is layer this way. You know, I don't know. Maybe it's a woman's fault
They should start acting like a real woman and not like a man
Much of trans genders, I mean without even being a
Trans genders, but it's like I mean I'd rather pay out the drag queen than some of these some of these
You know like beta or man god Malacca. Yeah, I know what a Malacca is is male
I see body language I could it is I could it is him
I make a good you know, Apollo has a partner. He's a wonderful wife and Apollo
I love Apollo because God he told me he died and I like I mourn for him and then he was what
He said Apollo died and stuff and I was like
You came back to life, but then it's like but then other people like die. Yeah, I'm resurrected, you know, I'm
Resurrected, you know KZ was KZ died. He's died
Like it was a really and it's like now I was you know, he was so annoying to me
But it's like I can't believe he died and then I mean I feel bad
I deleted like this video I made of him where it kind of me. How do you know it's me?
I went multiple times to Turkey, but not the the prostitutes, no.
Even I've gone to a female prostitute and but I didn't have sex with her. I was wait what I think you're gay
I was on too much ecstasy. I know but I was that I was in Amsterdam and the red light district and I was hanging out with some guys
Oh, yeah, yeah shy
I just went in yeah, I went first this one late. She's very beautiful, but I was like on too much ecstasy
Oh, when I was single and young I went there with some friends, you know because I was living near
near the border to Netherlands
Man
Neverland Ranch Michael Jackson's place. Oh
No, I thought you said never Netherlands. No, no, no, no Holland or how you say
Hey, you know Holland was made by sticking your finger in a dyke
No, yeah, it's made from Dykes it was it used to be a swamp and then they raise it from the swamp
Yeah, I know it's below below sea level. Yeah
But the guy that put his finger on the dike, he was over 18, so don't worry you guys, okay?
Crickets, I just heard crickets? Okay, I'm sorry.
No, you don't. It's my, the Greeks want to make a
kebab out of you.
They want to make, the Greeks want to remain to fetish cheese basically, but you know what?
Put some Kalamata olives in my butt, and we'll all have fun.
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
You are a man, this makes you a man.
Jesus, what's going on?
And you're gonna,
the goddess Athena is gonna fucking take a revenge upon you.
And you're out of luck, I'm sorry.
So basically, he's my say,
he's a pervert who put his dick out in public.
That's what he's saying.
Was there children around?
Oh my God, there's children around.
That's sure. See that's no no no I pretend you to be to be Christine. He's my he's a
He's a
Pervert you show she's my
She
I make I make no
Yeah
He put his dick out in public and show it to kids Christine
Get him Christine. He smile is a pervert for show exhibitionist. He shows penis on the little kids in public
That's what that's what's the same that goes. It's the same example. Hello, we got it. We got it. We got it
You understand that's how stupid some of the shit sounds to me. So it's like when yeah, yeah
I know it's crazy, and I okay the twist anything to make to make drama out of it, you know, yeah
And it's like, you know, and sometimes people like, you know, are just like being defensive because they've had stuff said about them.
And then it's like, then they get attention off of them by making, they're making someone worse. Right.
And it's like, everyone likes to like try to level and stuff like that.
How about like, you know, we're all imperfect human beings.
And it's like, as long as we haven't like, you know, violently, you know, great someone then.
Basically we're doing okay. I mean it's like we're murdered somebody. I mean it's like those are the things like but like actually like you know hurting people like
I don't know. It's like, you know, someone's seeing something on the internet. Oh my god. Oh, you know, like
That's like, you know, basically Crystal Marie was like, oh
Oh, we got a let's take out their eyeballs and like, you know, like the scar their face and I mean, it's like, oh my god
There's these disgusting
violent fantasies of these
Great, I mean, there's people are insane is it basically I'm like afraid of
I don't know if it's republicans or what but it's like there's something fucking wrong with some people. I don't I don't know
In securities, trust me. They are so insecure. I have to deal with some of these people on tbp
Screamers and all kind of shit, you know, and they say the most ridiculous shit, you know
I don't even want to repeat it, you know someone someone
And trust me if if you give them a little bit of their own medicine back
And Christine, we're on the way.
Summer, we're on the way.
They cry.
How dare you?
Oh, my god.
Yeah.
How dare you make me look like an old lady?
I'm a woman.
So what if you're a woman?
I mean, Jesus Christ.
Sike, Sike, Sike.
I mean, have you seen Christy?
You know, three women fight it for so long
to get equal rights.
And if you give them the equal rights, you know,
equal behavior, then they could,
they pay the woman card.
So what?
You want to be equal?
You want-
They can't take it.
They don't like a taste of their own medicine, right?
Exactly.
They dish out, they can take it.
Yeah, and I give Christine on KPP their own medicine her own medicine and she's still cry about it
She's still cry about it
That's what I basically done. I didn't I didn't curse at air. I didn't call her any names
I didn't call the B or R what nothing. I just give her all medicine
And she's still mad about it, right? And she called me all kind of things
They'll she'll hit you forever for it. I mean, it's like you'll never they'll never forget and it's like there's nothing
There's no forgive
They'll just be like constantly bringing up
Years ago, but if you bring up something. Oh, that was years ago. That was that was yeah, but they do the same
They do the same. That's your childhood. It's like oh my god. I mean it'll go back so far. We're like, I don't I don't remember
We're different people at different times in our lives right like we people that's the thing people can grow and learn from their mistakes
They don't need to like exactly. Oh, so I'm so dirty. Well, do you know if I take a bath?
I'm not dirty anymore, but it's like I can't take enough baths to ever be said. Oh, he has
Oh, yeah, the better victims. I'm so disgusting, right?
Listen, let me say this one this one only okay. Listen
You know, when I wasn't TVP with a gang of Sama and Christine, you know, they use all these insecure men, you know
All these were beta mates and you know what one of them
Christine caught
Wait, wait, let me finish please. She called the family member the best friend and you know when they say
They say things about my mother was dead. Okay. Oh, I'm gonna dig out your mother of her grave and ask rate them
I'm gonna yeah, yeah, yeah, and I'm gonna
Because I'd say it it was my my fault. I didn't know I was you I said I have two two daughters and shit and this guy
Oh, I want to fistfuck your daughter's in the ass until they scream. I'm gonna
I'm gonna ask fuck them in front of a burning cross and shit, you know, and Christine and
some more.
Yeah, yeah.
Tell him.
They gaslighting him.
And he ever called them their friends.
Listen.
So if they call you pedophile protector, what should I call Christine then by, by, uh, by
supporting, uh, a pedophile to or even now?
Exactly.
Oh, well, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
Oh, I'm just kidding. I don't really...
Exactly.
And they still talk about letting them on the panel.
They still let him show Christine
is the pedophile protector too, then.
Oh, yeah. They all are.
I mean, it's like, I mean, Bita told me,
oh, don't have LD on your show.
No, no, he's bad. He's a PDF.
Exactly.
He hasn't on our show still.
I mean, it's like...
But he's not as bad as this one. I'm not gonna go through and measure every like little detail of every every accused crime
Right, it's like fucking like I don't care. Yeah, they're not fucking in my house
They're not fucking I'm not worried about it. It's like they're other fucking people on the internet
We're going through TV screens. It's like we jump out through the TV screen like really
i don't fucking care it's okay listen to to sort out uh if someone is really a pedophile or if
someone that's really really something really bad okay take them out but the same thing about
anyone they're not gonna be running around on youtube i mean it's like they'd be on youtube if
they really that i mean it's like really i mean it's like uh i mean it's just so i mean people are
how stupid americans are to take someone that is like semen or christine serious
semen and beta are like oh semen and beta oh every oh my god we love if somebody is fucking
semen no beta is not that bad beta beta is not that bad she don't go too far she don't go too far
i think she got she got she get used she get used by this idiot by christine by by semen
Can you read it?
I think you and Peter are similar in the character.
You don't have bad intentions.
Bite your tongue.
Hold on.
But I'll shoot my.
Because I had the tattoo, and then she constantly,
oh, look at his tattoo.
Oh, he's going to have my name forever, or everyone on him.
And so then I said, OK, well, I'm going to turn it around,
and I'm going to have the tattoo modified.
And so it bright.
So I got it modified.
Can you read it yet?
Hold on.
Here we go.
I don't know man see what I did no what you can't read it
You read it wait where look at the screen fuck
Wait what you have to talk to a pizza. Yeah
Oh
I like the humor behind it.
There's humor behind it.
I took lemons and I made a fucking B to A.
It is the last bastion of your soul thing in it as well.
Why don't you go fucking marry her?
Bitch.
Oh.
Bitch?
Yeah, I think that is in love with B to A.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, is that your...
Moment, I'm coming.
Okay, I have to go.
Well, I'm nice talking to you. I'm gonna play the instrument for everybody. I
Have to go have a good day Apollo. Thank you. I'm playing the lyre for you. I'm playing the lyre
Thank you Apollo. Hey guys, I'm in a new I'm in a cool new video too. Let's watch a cool new video. This is my new
This is kind of about the occult a little bit. It's pretty cool
Watch it
You
Okay, what are you trying to end? What's going on? Oh, hi. Hi. Yeah, you like that one. It's pretty good
I've been doing like some like monkey a Billy and
Based up lately, but let me let me see what I got
Do I have anything else? I
Mean yeah, I do I mean
And this one wants to come up with a link up if you want to
In Mother's Day, by the way, it's Mother's Day kiss you. I'll kiss you
Just like do I kiss your white Vaj? Thank you so much. I appreciate that
Shamrock, thank you so much kiddy respects. Yep. I mean hey my kid is my kid is very
Be this on the hearts of men. Oh, well, whatever
What do you see that catfish in person and not person but just even her real picture?
Go beat a your meter
Okay, let me see what I got
Um, how about, um, this is my, um, this is called Underground Streamer Panes.
Um, it's pretty good.
How do I open this? Share, share, copy link.
I'll get shareable link. Okay, got it.
This is a really good one, kind of based on 80s TV theme songs,
called Underground Schumer Pains, like growing pains, right?
Look up from another one of Psyche's midnight fright displays
Please exactly normal
That's our favorite thing
We laugh like saints with eyeliner
And a phone that never rings
Show me that smile again
Even if the whole thing's worth it
Down here where the strange ones grin
The coats go in
Nightmares, robes, and necks stuck in
The cults going underground again
Psychies have nightmares, but he's hosting them with John
Reading cards at breakfast like disaster is a farm
Someone hit the relics in the laundry by the stairs
Someone's acting casual while conducting psychic prayers
And someone in the candle smug behind the secret door
high priestess knows a little something more. She never makes an entrance, she just suddenly
appears. Specs is everybody's chaos with the whisper in their ears.
Show me that smile again. Even if your halo's looking bent, we're the ones that daylight
I can't laugh like the Apocalypse's friends with secret rights and bargain bingems
The cold's going underground again
Underground, underground, keep it cozy, keep it strange
Every hearted little heart in here is overdue for change
If the world gets loud above us, let it spin and make a fuss
We've got one secret
high priestess as she's bowing
judging us
show me
that smile again
flash it like a sweet
forbidden hymn
psyche dreams but we
don't break within
the cults going underground
again
show me
that smile again
come on in
bring your eyeball friends
This cracks, we still descend, the cold's going underground again, yeah, the cold's going underground again.
What you're whitey Ford who's whitey Ford you calling me whitey?
As white as the comb
Let's see what else I got
hmm
I had the buddy troll song that's pretty good if you want to hear the buddy troll song oh
You're purring you're purring. I do have the buddy troll song
Ba de tro ba de tro de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de
oh shit here shenanigans huh don't show that again okay there we go but the troll but the
troll meh meh meh meh here we go oh i got it
where is it click click click click click click click click come on i'm a bit midnight a bit midnight
Where the fuck is it?
There's so many fucking I have like a hundred tabs open right now. I think literally
I'm gonna start closing I'll find it eventually that do it that that that that that that oh got it
See it, okay
Seekers in survive
Tonight it's better when they're smiling
No horns, no pitchfork, no open hay
Just five questions and a cool bond
For betrayal
Da-de-na-na da-de-na-na da-de-na-na da-de-na-na
you're slid and soft with the halo too
just checking on you reloaded blue
you said i care you said i see
you brought fake loyalty wholesale tax free
you'll learn my wounds you'll learn my math
you're not real hard then set the trap
You call it concern, and I call it death You leave with screenshots tucked in your chest
You want the T, the keys, the codes, the private play, the hidden roads
Not here to heal, not here to build Just here to see where the arm is
Too many questions, not enough so Too much sugar in the casserole
Too much on neutral, too much on good, too much smoke for the nice guy
But detro, but detro, this is cool, cool in the friendship
Bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, smile in the front little knife in the shop
Act so worried while they gossip to all
But detro, but detro, they don't matter at the empathy
We got a friend near the temple called Jucaia, Jucaia, false little friend, you won't get far
Got an eye, spin that crow, everybody watch the bloody troll
Jucaia, Jucaia, false little friend, you won't get far
Got an eye, spin that crow, first they fly, then they pry
Who said what? Put the saintly eye
Not to stir things, that old routine
Kerosene
They whisper here
Then drift right there
Dropping concern
Like polluted air
Person A
Gets us spiced up
Quote
Person B
Gets us soft enough
Person C gets a hate all drama First I'm the department of manufactured karma
Now the roof is where the wires are crossed Trust gets taxed and the vibe gets lost
That's not magic with a sleight of hand Pursue a wizard with a needy brand
Can't build a stage, can't own a room So they brand free space
And other folks too I'm always nearby when the mess appears
Always so shocked with crocodile tears Always protecting, always concerned
Funny how bridges behind them burn But they troll, but they
friendship roll oh oh oh smile in the front little knife in the shop acts so
worried while they gossip to all but they troll but they troll and they do you
leave at the van where bull oh oh oh oh glitter on top but the core is small fake
ass friend near the temple call
this pain repackage truth and sell the stain danger to they split the crew make folks doubt what they
already knew danger three they pay reaction them point and scream look bad attraction no sweetheart
you build the maze they acting scared of the fire you raise danger for they drain your heart
typically your focus part by part not always trying to win the war sometimes they just want
a rectal floor what's the cure slow that trust what's the tip patterns first what's the rule
Won't mind your hurt for a social trick
Won't play translate a priest since I won't hug you close while sharpening lies
A real friend comes a fake one, stirs a real friend, asks a fake one
There's a real friend keeps the chamber sealed
A fake one wants your wounds revealed
So if they rush like this in these crone
With hungry eyes and a borrowed tone
Don't hand them candles, keys or gold
Some demons freeze when the door gets closed
But detrol, but detrol
Cheap little ghoul in a satin robe
Walk slick through the loophole
Till the lies come up and we name it
All Buddy Troll, Buddy Troll
All familiar with the hungry soul
You wanna hear the temple, the map, the scroll
Now dance back out through the banishment hole
Up didn't did not, up didn't did not
No more entry, not at all
Truth is hotter than a mirror ball
Truth a yard, out your road
Exit left, little Buddy Troll
Smile all you want
We know the road case closed on a Buddy Troll
What are we doing? I'll put the link up one more time.
One final link here. I'll take it off.
One more link.
Who's going to come up here? Everyone's a fucking pussy.
Get up here, pussies. You're all a bunch of pussies.
Not all of you. Some of you are dicks.
I'm just kidding. No, I'm not. But maybe I am.
You'll never know.
Maybe I've been buddy-trolling you
maybe
Probably not but
What is this one? This is good. I haven't seen this in a while
So good a little lullaby for you lulla. Bye. Bye
Lulla bisexuals
Bye don't let the door hit your ass on the way out
Night turns the key in the hush of the hall
She feels the universe lean when he calls
They taught him the world is a cage made of shut
A calendar heartbeat, a clock made of wood
But he found a small doorway in starlit mistakes
And it opened them all
And her true name, Milwaukee, is Psych
He gathers the light, thinks it's lust
He cradles the questions, the shimmer
And cause she takes all this grief
And she spins it like gold
Till it warms like a secret
The dark can't withhold
And every time the sky forgets
How to shine, he whispers
Hold on, this miracle's mine
She walks like a blessing to learn how to move
When the world gets loud and the stars feel far
She turns all his fear into bright white sparks
The spell he doesn't have to explain
She's the soft thunder living in his veins
His love is a doorway, fate is a thread
She's the moonlight, stitching the torrent to the light
Some days he is glass with a storm in his chest. Some days he's a lighthouse, the one that rests from the cliffs of his past.
He watched shadow swim, but she laughed in the darkness. Remembered it's him.
Her hands are small galaxies, brave and unshy. She carries his night like a crown in her eye.
and swears the whole cosmos gets quiet to hear how we can speak to the silence like it's a
dear friend so if they try calling you dumb and brand new tell them i'm not for your judgments
i'm someone that's true yeah his magical daughter midnight and bloom she walks like a
The world gets loud and the stars feel far
She turns all his fear into bright white sparks
This belly doesn't have to explain
She's the soft, thunder-living in his veins
If love is a doorway, fate is a threat
She's the moonlight stitching the torn to the black
for signs in the street lights for hands on his pain
but wonders not thunder, it's quieter than that
it's the way we say moment, I'm tiptoes back
so he'll build her a harbor from lullabies and flame
from you who are enough and you don't have to change
and when she outgrows every room he can make
may she keep one small truth that the darkness can't take
There is magic in breath and bruises that mend in the brave way they lost
And the stars feel far
She turns all his fear into bright white sparks
If the universe ever acts who he is
Say he's psychic, he makes constellations by hand
If love is a doorway, fate is a thread
He's the moonlight stitching the torn to the lid
you guys go. Well, you can go in whenever you want, of course. I'm not holding you here.
I mean, come here if you're on free will. Browser would block my screen. Okay. Let me
Let's see.
I'm a scapegoat. Yeah, this is good. I'm a scapegoat, you know. I'm a goat. I'm not gonna escape.
Hence the scapegoat. You have fun hanging out. Have a good night. Have a fun, or a good morning,
or whatever day it is. Whatever you are, whatever you are in this world, you have a wonderful day.
Love you.
They gather in a circle with their clean hands and sharpened teeth
Talking holy, talking noble while they feed on something weak
They don't need truth, they need a target someone tender they can blame
They make communion out of cruelty
And call the fire by my name
They love a sacrificial victim
They love a soft and open throat
They build their little bond on hatred
And then they crown escape gold
They pick the kind the one's still human
The one with mercy in their bones
Then tear them down to feel like giants
But I'm not your normal girl
Project army they never become what you are not
That caused it so.
Walking through the rain, I go my own way.
Pass the teeth and pass the blade.
I go my own way.
Let them gossip, let them glow.
They can keep their little pasture.
I was never made for them.
Things you couldn't keep
The walls would breathe in slow and low
Every secret you don't show
Every version left behind
Still alive inside your mind
You said, am I the one who's dream?
You are something else, wearing pieces of yourself
Faces hanging in the air
Try them on if you still care
Every mask of life you wore
Every life still wanting more
You said something's always watching
I said yes!
So is your-
They speak permission dressed is just be me timing tight reactions trained nothing random in this game
Subtle cues, micro smirks decide your views
One cold pause can shut it down
One wrong step, you're out the crowd
They don't force you, they don't need to
You edit what you're allowed to
No chains wrapped around your wrists
Just consequences if you twist
That's a trade, I'm glad to deal
You call it paranoia, I call it psych
You learn comfort, I learn fight
Strings in the ceiling, cutting lows
Nothing left for me to lose if it breaks
When truth is said, it was already hanging dead
They don't silence you
They make you silence yourself
To fit your frame. I won't play your quiet game boundaries clean no disguise no more
magic in my veins but it feels like a curse they told me power is a tool in your hands
but every step forward just strikes me through dirt didn't come here to be a hero
didn't come here to play and say now i'm carving out a future with the blade i didn't make
clearly crawling under my skin something waking deep within if this
I'm still lucky
Marble smiles in polished streets.
Every gate says someone's watching you.
Every nod asks, what can you do?
Rufa says, keep breathing, keep your answers clean.
Easy words from someone known and seen,
but no one knows what's going on.
State your name, state your rank, state your claim to standing here.
Every proof it sounds polite and every smile says disappear.
Welcome to the city of, welcome to the city of smiles and eyes
Then walks a storybook and polished white
Humphrey shining like the
Shoulder chaos with a grin
Tiny dragon, this gets on the wind
Biscuits, pasting, perfect timing
Too soon to get
Can't keep a level view
He looks at me and doesn't look away
Doesn't smile like he's passing what I pray
Maybe friendship starts in places like this
Two men being judged in the same abyss
He plays by the book
I've been the pitchies of night and form, I'm a glitch in the game, but the room reads both with a butcher's eye,
Sorting who can serve and who can die.
Welcome to the city of smiles and eyes,
Sign here if you wanna live, badge and seal, line and file,
Stand up straight and wait a while, prove your worth, declare your name,
Everything here's a measure game.
And still they watch like I'm lying
I don't know what I'm
Welcome to the city of smile
Average in the known classification, unhelpful potential
I trust in me, sort me, size me, test me, dress me up in words
And still not get me, I cross blood and desert
Just to arrive, paperwork's not what'll eat me alive
Welcome to the city of smiles and knives
Sign here if you wanna live, badge and seal, line and file
Hold your nerve and fake just-
whole damn city try me welcome to the city of smiles welcome to the city of
smiles
Ink dries fast on borrowed names, but mine still bites the same
Gather around the fire, hear the desert's tale
of a marble cut village where the dry winds used to wail they had a magic
waterfall that poured out from the sky a doorway into elsewhere that never once
ran dry but miracles have teeth my friends they always take their toll and
sometimes from that shining place comes something dark and cold the water
the blue light turned to gray and something made of shell and teeth came crawling out to play
old Hiram drew his hunting knife expecting just to die but standing right beside him was a stranger
passing by a skinny sharp-tongued outworlder with a bone-white poison blade who grinned into the jaws
If the shadows rise, we strike for it
We stand where the elsewhere splits the sky
And laugh while the monsters try
No gold, no glory, calling through
We're just stubborn hawks that see it through
If the waters curse, we fight for it
Yeah, someone has to
He wasn't clad in iron, he had no righteous vow
Just an ordinary man who wouldn't bow down now
He took the heavy crushing blows to keep the guard alive
And cracked a stupid joke just so they both survived
He fought through claw and carapace, through poison, pain and scale
And when the monster finally broke, he didn't cheer
took a stand like maybe true nobility is just where you land it wasn't just the
battle that made the village smile it's the way he stayed shared the spoils
and lingered for a while a stone of power left behind a promise
Boring spies talk softly through the night and show them there are kind of ways for someone built to fight
They say
The elsewhere splits the sky and laugh while the monsters try
But something in that desert changed, and the road goes on.
And the story's only just begun.
The doors stood open, the tunnel ran clear, the chanting faded, no footsteps were near,
the desert lay waiting beyond the black night, no one would blame him for fleeing the fight.
The shadows would hide him, the road would be wide, he'd live if he left all the screaming behind,
but far down the stair where the red torches burned,
Now fear is a whisper that says just survive
No one would know if you walked out alive
But some choices echo long after they're made
And cowardly silence is harder to fade
So he turned back around in the belly of hell
Draining his safety for a story to tell
Call him a fool or an out-worlder stray
But he was not the kind who would wa-
was near but heroes are born when they turn toward their fear though night was
hungry and blood would be drawn and he stood with the helbrus and waited for
dawn
back through the tunnels where cold echoes lay with keys and his trembling
hands leading the way iron bar cages and ice filled with dread
The souls who believed they were already dead
A leonid giant with fury and mane
A noble-born swordsman still bound in his chain
A fire-bright major stared hard through the gloom
And wondered what madman had walked to their doom
They asked him his name while the torch is still burning
And stared like a madman who foolishly turned
No prophecy named him
But he was not the kind who would walk away
The door stood open, the desert was near
But heroes are born when they turn toward their fear
And though night was hungry, and blood would be drawn
He stood with the helpless and waited for dawn
when the darkness takes hold for courage is really a shining command it's one stubborn step when you
don't understand and the bards still sing when the taverns are loud of a strange young outworlder who
Yes, he turned back around in the belly of hell, trading his safety for a story to tell.
Call him a fool or an outworlder stray, but he was not the kind who would walk away.
The door stood open, the desert was near, the heroes are born when they turn toward their fear.
And though night was hungry and blood would be drawn, he stood with his allies and fought till the dawn.
When the fire burns low for the man who turned where most would not go the tale of that toy still travels afar
The night he became
an outward
Every shadow twists and turns
Circle strong and national bone
They say tonight I'm not going home
Nights like tea and hungry hands
Whifters echo through the sand
They think they're great
You think the night belongs to you?
about silhouettes in key they trust their knives more than their brains all it takes is one mistake
one broken step one shattered chain the circle cracks the torch is fall the nighter ups I break
it off your perfect ritual comes undone the prey you call
Not sure how far in tonight I'm the problem you saw
Maybe this is where I change Maybe blood will mark my name
But monsters wearing sacred lies still look the same
And different eyes and if survival has a cause
I'll let your fear and state
I'm not your all away home tonight
I'm the problem you saw me
Cold grass under my back, strange sky overhead
No memory of the road had led me here instead
A window in the air says quest accepted bright
Apparently survival is tonight's first fight
Cold grass under my back, strange sky overhead
No memory of a row that led me here instead
A window in the air says quest accepted right
Apparently survival is tonight's first fight
No sword, no map, no clue what game I'm in
Just monsters in the hedges and a message made of wind
A voice that isn't speaking but it's judging all the same
Self decided, I'm a player in it's game
Alright then, Faye, if that's how you play
Throw me in the fire, see if I'll stay
Trust me in the abyss
If you must let the monsters circle in the dust
Write your rules across the sky tonight
But I'm not going down without a fight
Laughing in the dark because
I can't survive first, understand the plan, call it destiny or cosmic chance, but I'm walking out of here in pants.
Quest reward trousers, now we're talking sense, finally the universe shows basic competence.
Shadows in the leaves
Every rustle sounds like something with too many teeth
But panic's just a luxury I can't afford to buy
So I grin at the darkness and I ask the system why
No guidebook here, no kindly NPCs
A monster circled in the dust
Right to rules across the sky tonight
But I'm not going down without a fight
Laughing in the dark because
I can't survive first
Understand the plan
Call it destiny or cosmic chance
But I'm walking out of-
Every quest a step through fear, every joke a shield right here, because Carrick sometimes looks absurd, like arguing with a glowing-
If you must let the monster circle in the dust write your rules across the sky tonight, but I'm not going down without a fight
Laughing in the dark because I can't survive first understand the plan this world may think it holds the dance
But I'm walking out of here
Strange, certain spans, first class, complete.
It's like burns, every shadow twists and turns
Circle strong, and national bone
They say tonight, I'm not going home
Nights like tea, and hungry, and whifters echo through
He thinks of driving, don't love to fight, but break him by.
You think the night belongs to you, but monsters fall.
about silhouettes and kings they trust their knives more than their brains all it takes is one
mistake one broken step one shattered chain the circle cracks the torch is fall the nighter
wraps up break it off your perfect ritual comes undone the prey you
I'm not your offering tonight, I'm the problem you some, maybe this is where I change, maybe blood will mark my name, but monsters wearing sacred lies still look the same in different eyes, and if survival has accru-
Your God is silent, your fear and state
I'm not your all-over tone tonight
I'm the problem, you summer
The stone doors stood open, the tunnel ran clear
The chanting faded, no footsteps were near
The desert lay waiting beyond the black night
And no one would blame him for fleeing the fight
The shadows would hide him, the road would be wide
He'd live if he left all the screaming behind
But far down the stair where the red torches burned
Now fear is a whisper that says, just survive.
No one would know if you walked out alive.
But some choices echo long after they're made.
And cowardly silence is harder to fade.
So he turned back around in the belly of hell.
Draining his safety for a story to tell.
Call him a fool or an out-worlder stray.
But he was not the kind who would walk away.
was near. But heroes are born when they turn toward their fear. Though night was hungry
and blood would be drawn, he stood with the helpless and waited for dawn.
Back through the tunnels where cold echoes lay, with keys in his trembling hands leading
the way. Iron bar cages and ice filled with dread, souls who believed they were already
Giant with fury and mane. A noble barn swordsman still abounded his chain. A fire bright major stared hard through the gloom, and wondered what madman had walked to their doom. They asked him his name while the torch is still burning, and stared like a madman who foolishly turned. No prophecy named him, no legends foretold, just courage enough to stand fast in the cold.
was not the kind who would walk away. The door still opened, the desert was near,
but heroes are born when they turn for their fear. And though night was hungry and blood would
be drawn, he stood with the helpless and waited for dawn.
darkness takes hold, for courage is really a shining command.
It's one stubborn step when you don't understand.
And the bards still sing when the taverns are loud,
of the strange young outworlder who would not bow.
in the belly of hell trading his safety for a story to tell call him a fool or an outworlder stray
but he was not the kind who would walk away the door stood open the desert was near the heroes
are born when they turn toward their fear and though night was hungry and blood would be drawn
he stood with his allies and fought till the dawn
The fire burns low for the man who turned where most would not go
The tale of that choice still travels afar
The night he became